<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><jobs><job><id>IRC27419</id><title>Research Support Associate, CRISPR and Genome Editing</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27419&amp;p_spid=1095122</url><publish_date>14-Dec-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Gene Targeting Resource Center</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description></department_description><detailed_description>The Research Support Associate will join a team of experts in gene editing in mammalian cells and mouse embryos. Will work with the CRISPR and Genome Editing Resource Center (CGERC) Director to define and assess the feasibility of new applications to the CGERC&apos;s mission. Responsibilities include participating in the design and documentation of the CGERC projects and learning newly published technology in related fields.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required. Must be comfortable working with mice. Experience with mammalian tissue culture, Southern analysis, and molecular cloning preferred. Must have the ability to analyze scientific data and solve experimental problems independently.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required, including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27470</id><title>Optical Engineer</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27470&amp;p_spid=1097133</url><publish_date>05-Jan-2022</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Bio-Imaging Resource Center</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>We provide members of the University and their visitors with a wide spectrum of microscopy equipment and image analysis software packages, together with extensive training in their use. Systems include state-of-the-art optical imaging using widefield, confocal, multiphoton, light-sheet and super-resolution microscopy. We also provide consultation on sample preparation and immunolabeling procedures. We train researchers to use the microscopes and image acquisition software themselves, providing assistance when necessary to ensure collection of high quality images. Staff also conduct more complex work on a collaborative basis with the scientists.  The center currently houses several widefield fluorescence/transmitted light microscopes (Zeiss and Olympus), two DeltaVision Image Restoration microscopes (API/GE Healthcare), three laser scanning confocal microscopes (a Zeiss LSM 780, a Leica SP8 and a Zeiss LSM 880 NLO system), a Yokagawa spinning disk confocal microscope (Zeiss/Spectral Applied), an FV1000MPE Twin upright multiphoton system (Olympus), a multi-line STORM/TIRF system (Nikon) fitted with widefield-FLIM and TIRF-FLIM capabilities (Lambert Instruments), an LCV110 VivaView; Incubator Microscope (Olympus), a Yokawawa CV1000 CellVoyager; environmental spinning disk system (Olympus), an Ultramicroscope light sheet system (LaVision BioTec), a laser microdissection system (MMI), and an OMX 3D-SIM super-resolution microscope (API/GE Healthcare). Most of the systems are fitted with environmental chambers for live cell imaging.  The center has five full-time research support staff including the director. The center is staffed during business hours and under an open-access model, trained investigators can use the facility 24/7. In addition, many of the systems can be operated remotely via the center&apos;s on-line facility management software.</department_description><detailed_description>Funded initially by a five-year Beckman Foundation grant to the Rockefeller University, the Optical Engineer will contribute to the development of a new, integrated platform for the acquisition and analysis of data from pre-commercial light-sheet instruments for microscopy on living organisms and cells. The Optical Engineer will work in close collaboration with optical microscopy and image analysis staff, biologists, physicists, bioinformaticians, computer scientists, and precision instrumentation fabrication experts in an international and interdisciplinary environment. Responsibilities include maintaining and modifying pre-commercial light sheet microscopes as required and training researchers in their use. As a staff member in the Bio-Imaging Resource Center (BIRC), will liaise between the research scientists, the existing microscopy and image analysis staff, and a new advanced image analyst who will implement deep learning-based approaches to analyze the light-sheet data. The instruments will be built in a dedicated new laboratory space housed on bedrock underneath the existing BIRC laboratory. Light sheet systems to be established will be pre-commercial systems such as the Lattice Light Sheet and MOSAIC systems, using designs kindly provided by the Janelia Research Campus. Additional responsibilities include implementing other pre-commercial systems in due course, as well as executing custom modifications of other BIRC microscopes as required.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Ph.D. or equivalent in optical engineering, physics, biophysics, or related field required. Experience in programming scientific instrumentation, teaching, and training a must. Must have a broad understanding of optical imaging techniques and the ability to build bespoke microscopes or other instruments from scratch. Must have a working knowledge of image and data acquisition, preferably with imaging biological samples. Must be enthusiastic, rigorous, motivated, have excellent interpersonal and communication skills. Must work well with a team in a service-oriented environment. Must be a self-starter with a proven ability to initiate collaborative projects and to introduce biologists to complex equipment. Must have the ability to establish close networks with colleagues nationwide involved in similar projects as this senior position will involve a significant degree of autonomy.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC26913</id><title>Research Specialist</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=26913&amp;p_spid=1071096</url><publish_date>15-Sep-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Laboratory of Single-Cell Genomics and Population Dynamics</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>The Laboratory of Single-cell Genomics and Population Dynamics investigates how a cell population maintains homeostasis at whole-organism scale and how it is disrupted in cancer and aging-related disorders. Our primary approach is to develop state-of-the-art genomic techniques to profile and perturb cell dynamics at single-cell resolution. Our long-term goal is to leverage this knowledge to develop cell-type-specific engineering tools that enhance cell population robustness or restore cell population homeostasis in response to cancer and aging-related disorders.</department_description><detailed_description>The responsibilities of the research specialist include mouse colony maintenance, including assessment of status and health of laboratory animal colonies through weekly maintenance; performing surgical procedures on mice along with administering chemicals; genotyping, euthanasia, dissection, and collection of tissue samples for further analysis; and maintenance of all documentation and records for the animal colony. Will perform imaging validation, including preparing frozen sections utilizing a cryostat; examining markers through fluorescent microscopy; performing routine procedures such as immunohistochemistry and fluorescent in situ hybridization on the mouse and human tissue (e.g., frozen and fixed tissues). Will also manage maintenance and repair of laboratory equipment, and maintain reagents and supply inventory following department procedures.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required. Must have experience working with mice and with pathology. Must have a minimum of one year of experience with mouse colony management, genotyping, and experiments, working knowledge of basic procedures involved in immunohistochemistry and mammalian tissue pathology, and excellent organizational and communication skills.  Must be highly motivated and can work in a team environment.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC26718</id><title>Grant Proposal Writer</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=26718&amp;p_spid=1062081</url><publish_date>28-Jul-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Neurogenetics of Language</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Development/Events/Writer/Grants Management</professional_area><department_description>The ability to speak has allowed our species to pass knowledge between generations, articulate complex ideas, and building societies. Our lab uses song-learning birds and other species as models to study the molecular and genetic mechanisms that underlie vocal learning, including how humans learn spoken language. We are interested in how their brains, and ours, have evolved to produce this complex behavior.</department_description><detailed_description>The Grant Proposal Writer will be responsible for providing grant writing support to the investigators of the laboratory, overseeing, and managing an extensive grant portfolio, and interacting with multiple collaborators and institutions with the primary goal of acquiring funding for the lab and consortium research efforts. The Grant Proposal Writer will assist with searching for, preparing, and submitting grant applications and progress reports, ensuring that deadlines are met, and that required information is provided in the appropriate format. Will support lab members with editing individual proposals, manuscripts, and posters, work collaboratively with the Office of Sponsored Research to ensure timely turnaround and proposal submissions and contribute to developing feasible novel ideas in grant proposals. If funded and researchers test the ideas, the candidate would be credited by authorship in subsequent publications.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Ph.D. in science required. Experience in research and an academic environment is necessary. Must have experience in neuroscience, genomics, and/or computational biology. Extensive knowledge in the scientific granting process and successful writing on grant proposals for scientific research, including submissions for federal (e.g., NIH and HSF) organizations, private foundations, and donors required. Strong writing and computer skills, including demonstrated proficiency with Microsoft Office applications, are necessary. Must have excellent communication skills and the ability to use good judgment in working independently, showing initiative, managing deadlines, and responding to inquiries. Must be excited to work as an integral member of a highly productive and close-knit team and be willing to take on a broad range of tasks.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment.  Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27099</id><title>Research Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27099&amp;p_spid=1080102</url><publish_date>18-Oct-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Chemical Immunology and Proteomics</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>The Laboratory of Chemical Immunology and Proteomics applies synthetic chemistry, chemical biology, and proteomics methods toward the goals of discovering and characterizing (a) novel selective chemical probes that perturb the functions of key proteins regulating immunological and neuroimmunological processes; (b) new mechanisms for small molecule-induced protein degradation; and, more broadly, (c) the pharmacological landscape and signal transduction pathways in immune and neuroimmunological disorders. Achieving these objectives is enhanced through the development of new chemical scaffolds targeting cysteine and other nucleophilic residues. By developing and applying innovative chemical proteomic profiling technologies, we aim to enrich our understanding of the molecular differences between pathologic and physiologic states in immune cells and cells of the nervous system (including microglia and oligodendrocytes, which are implicated in the autoimmune disorder multiple sclerosis). The lab also plans to explore how those differences can be further leveraged from a pharmacological perspective for the development of new therapies that not only target specific immune cell subtypes, but also the defined activation states of these cells. Please see www.vinogradovalab.com for more information.</department_description><detailed_description>The Research Assistant will work with other lab members on a project involving development of new mouse models for chemical proteomic studies of neuroinflammation and functional validation of prioritized protein targets in primary immune cells and neuroglia. This research is highly collaborative and is expected to provide new insights into post-translational drivers of immune misregulation and opportunities for pharmacological modulation with small-molecule electrophiles.  The Research Assistant will be responsible for maintenance of mouse colonies, mouse dissection for collection of tissue samples, mouse genotyping, tail vein injection, subcutaneous and intraperitoneal injections, analytical techniques such as real-time quantitative PCR, Western blot analysis, and immunohistochemistry, and extraction of nucleic acids and proteins from mouse and cell culture samples. Future responsibilities will also include molecular biological approaches, including cloning and experiments with DNA, RNA, and proteins to support the lab&apos;s science. During the full length of the appointment, you will also work with several lab members to support general Laboratory operations in the areas of purchasing and laboratory organization.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science and previous biochemistry or cell biology experience is required. Mouse experience is a plus, but not a pre-requisite. Must be highly motivated and driven by scientific curiosity, possess excellent verbal, written, and electronic communication skills, and interact effectively in a collaborative work environment. Must have excellent organizational skills, including laboratory record keeping, data management, and prioritizing work to carry out complex experiments with extreme attention to detail. Previous independent research experience or extensive laboratory coursework is strongly preferred. Must be amenable to a changing work schedule that prioritizes experiments and often deviates from the standard 9 to 5 workday, occasionally including weekend hours.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27098</id><title>Mechanic</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27098&amp;p_spid=1080101</url><publish_date>12-Oct-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Housing</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Building and Grounds Maintenance</professional_area><department_description>Rockefeller University provides a variety of housing accommodations in support of the scientific needs of the University.  Apartments and dormitories are available to full-time faculty and students, and hotel accommodations are available for faculty and guests of the Rockefeller community.  The Housing Department provides a safe, secure, affordable residence that is conveniently located near the campus.  Most of the University&apos;s apartments are located in full-service apartment buildings, with door staff and a variety of amenities.  A few smaller apartment buildings are located within a short walking distance from campus.  Dormitories and guest accommodations are located on the main campus.  The Rockefeller campus is located on the Upper East Side, one of New York&apos;s most desirable residential neighborhoods.  The 45-person housing staff consists of a group of mechanics, porters, housekeepers, and doorpersons, a superintendent for each building, and an office staff to address administrative needs.</department_description><detailed_description>Rockefeller University provides a variety of housing accommodations in support of the scientific needs of the University. Apartments and dormitories are available to full-time faculty and students, and hotel accommodations are available for faculty and guests of the Rockefeller community. The Housing Department provides a safe, secure, affordable residence that is conveniently located near the campus. Most of the University&apos;s apartments are located in full-service apartment buildings, with door staff and a variety of amenities. A few smaller apartment buildings are located within a short walking distance from campus. Dormitories and guest accommodations are located on the main campus. The Rockefeller campus is located on the Upper East Side, one of New York&apos;s most desirable residential neighborhoods. The 45-person housing staff consists of a group of mechanics, porters, housekeepers, and doorpersons, a superintendent for each building, and an office staff to address administrative needs.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School or Trade School diploma or equivalent required. Must have three to five years of relevant experience in mechanical repair or any combination of experience and training which provides the required knowledge, skills and abilities. Must have a general knowledge of all building systems and mechanical equipment used in residential buildings, including locks, flooring, windows, plumbing, electricity and switches, alarms, steam traps, packing, pipes, and valves, HVAC systems, and all mechanical system. Must have the ability to interact courteously with tenants and get along well with others in the workgroup and the Housing Department.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC26677</id><title>Clinical Research Coordinator</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=26677&amp;p_spid=1060082</url><publish_date>22-Jul-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Hospital</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Healthcare - RNs &amp; Nurse Management</professional_area><department_description>The Rockefeller University Center for Clinical and Translational Science is devoted to maximizing the bidirectional opportunities for clinical and translational research. Building on Rockefeller University Hospital&apos;s illustrious history as the birthplace of American biomedical science and translational research, and funded in part by an NIH Center for Clinical and Translational Science Award (CTSA), the Center is designed to provide an optimal infrastructure to conduct clinical and translational research and to educate the next generation of physician-scientists committed to patient-oriented research.

The Center for Clinical and Translational Science continues Rockefeller University&apos;s tradition of focusing on the interface between scientific discovery, human pathophysiology, and novel diagnostic, preventative, and therapeutic strategies to benefit all of humanity.</department_description><detailed_description>The Clinical Research Coordinator will assist in leading investigators through the navigation process to develop investigator-initiated protocols.  Will help create protocols, consent forms, and other regulatory documents while assessing protocol feasibility and teaching investigators how to formulate electronic IRB submissions. The Clinical Research Coordinator will teach and guide investigative teams on how to conduct/implement research studies while incorporating ICH/GCP principles, including organizing initiation meetings, source documentation development, internal monitoring, adverse event reporting, and conducting participants visits. The Clinical Research Coordinator will advise investigative teams about assessing adverse events, deviations, protocol compliance, new regulations, etc. If the Clinical Research Coordinator is a Nurse Practitioner, they may be responsible for providing written orders of the participant&apos;s study visit to the nursing staff, conduct the study visit(s) as the LIP, follow-up with abnormal assessments and lab results, and notify the IRB about serious or unanticipated adverse events and protocol deviations.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree and CCRC certification required; Master&apos;s degree in nursing and Board-Certified Adult or Family NP strongly preferred. Educational emphasis in science or nursing is preferred. Must have a minimum of four years of clinical research coordinator experience, including research related in IND/IDE trials. Working knowledge of Good Clinical Practice (GCP) and FDA Guidelines and high proficiency with Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Databases, and spreadsheets) necessary. Must have excellent verbal and written communication skills. Must have excellent organizational skills with demonstrated ability to prioritize assignments, maintain workflow, and work productively in meeting critical deadlines.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment.  Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27517</id><title>Systems Analyst</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27517&amp;p_spid=1099140</url><publish_date>13-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Hospital Informatics</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Information Technology</professional_area><department_description>The Rockefeller University Hospital is funded by the National Institutes of Health and has 20 patient beds for clinical research. The Hospital provides researchers with an opportunity to conduct clinical studies, and offers both normal volunteers and people with diseases under study the opportunity to stay in the hospital and help to contribute to important advances in science. The Hospital has an inpatient unit as well as an outpatient center where prospective patients are screened and many outpatient studies are conducted.  The Hospital is staffed 24 hours a day with professional nurses and has nutritional research, social work, art and recreation departments, and a radiology suite as well as its own research pharmacy. Our staff hospitalist and on-call physicians provide additional medical support to the clinical research teams.  For more information, please see the hospital web site at: http://www.rucares.org/</department_description><detailed_description>The Informatics Systems Analyst will work with the Rockefeller University Hospital Informatics and the Center for Clinical and Translational Sciences (RUCCTS) Bioinformatics Core and report to the Director of RUCCTS BioInformatics and the IT Manager of Hospital Informatics. The Systems Analyst will be responsible for the University&apos;s site activity and deep level troubleshooting in the Accrual to Clinical Trials (ACT) network, installation, implementation, maintenance of Shared Health Research Information Network (SHRINE) and i2b2 systems, and Cerner Electronic Health Record. The Systems Analyst will design, develop, and operate a computational workflow to analyze NextGen sequencing data and provide technical support on integrating Center for Expanded Data Annotation and Retrieval (CEDAR) (metadata platform) into our Enhancing Scientific Rigor, Reproducibility, and Reporting (R3) data analysis workflow system.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree required; educational emphasis in computer science, engineering, or a related field (preferably in healthcare informatics or clinical research setting) strongly preferred. Must have a minimum of one year of scientific programming experience in a research setting, familiarity with server support/systems administration, knowledge in Linux/Unix systems scripting (bash, python, R, etc.), experience with database administration (SQL, Postgres, Oracle, etc.), experience with system upgrade workflow processes, networking skills (firewalls, proxies, certificate/encryption methods, port configuration), and experience with web services (Apache Tomcat, Axis, WildFly, JDKs). Must have strong technical and computer skills, including Microsoft Office, Excel, Word, PowerPoint, and Oracle/SQL, and familiarity with reporting tools, i.e., Crystal, Cerner DA2, Business Objects, BIRT, Jasper iReport, etc. Familiarity with server support/systems administration, experience with system upgrade workflow processes, ability to work within complex software environments, and ability to work well with the vendor, project team, consultants, IT staff, and end-users necessary. Experience with Cerner Electronic Health record and Power Trials application, 1-3+ years of system/network administration, workflow implementation, web development, HPC (High-performance Computing and Cloud Computing highly desirable. Knowledge of Data Warehousing concepts, visualization of data preferred. Must have exceptional written and verbal communication skills and work effectively with Research Investigators, Administrators, vendors, the project team, consultants, IT staff, and end-users. Must be motivated with a deep willingness to gain SME (subject matter expertise) in protocol development, study applications and submissions, and IRB (Institutional Review Board) workflows. Must possess the ability to work within complex software environments and have initiative, energy, creativity, and advanced analytical/technical skills.</job_requirements><additional_details>As a vital member of the Information Technology/Hospital Informatics team, the Systems Analyst will be required to be available to perform job-related duties during off-hours. In some instances, may be required to come to campus or provide off-site support during time outside of traditional working hours. This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27516</id><title>Part-time Infection Control Coordinator, (17.5 hrs/week)</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27516&amp;p_spid=1099139</url><publish_date>13-Jan-2022</publish_date><employment_type>Part Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Hospital</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Healthcare - RNs &amp; Nurse Management</professional_area><department_description>The Rockefeller University Hospital is funded by the National Institutes of Health and has 20 patient beds for clinical research. The Hospital provides researchers with an opportunity to conduct clinical studies, and offers both normal volunteers and people with diseases under study the opportunity to stay in the hospital and help to contribute to important advances in science. The Hospital has an inpatient unit as well as an outpatient center where prospective patients are screened and many outpatient studies are conducted. The Hospital is staffed 24 hours a day with professional nurses and has nutritional research, social work, art and recreation departments, and a radiology suite as well as its own research pharmacy. Our staff hospitalist and on-call physicians provide additional medical support to the clinical research teams.  For more information, please see the hospital web site at: http://www.rucares.org/</department_description><detailed_description>The Infection Control Coordinator will be responsible for the development, coordination, and oversight of an effective hospital-wide program for surveillance prevention and control of infections. The Infection Control Coordinator will work across hospital departments to develop infection control policies and practices; develop, review, and update policies and procedures related to infection prevention and control; and develop, coordinate and present infection prevention education programs to hospital staff and patients.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required; educational emphasis in nursing or other clinical fields preferred. Must be certified in Infection Prevention and Control (CIC). Must have robust data analysis and computer skills and strong communication and interpersonal skills.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27553</id><title>Project Coordinator</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27553&amp;p_spid=1101136</url><publish_date>19-Jan-2022</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Hospital Clinical Research Office</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Healthcare - Business Office and Finance</professional_area><department_description>The Project Coordinator (PC) will play a critical role in the operationalization and execution of a four-year NIH-funded award, &apos;Empowering the Participant Voice.&amp;quot; The project leverages collaboration among investigators at six academic research sites to collect actionable participant feedback about their research experiences for institutional performance improvement. The project will incorporate a local investigator, leadership, and community stakeholder input to optimize the new infrastructure&apos;s framework, standards, build-out, and implementation. Our major initiative entering Year 3 is to engage early adopters for our new round of demonstration projects and ensure their national dissemination readiness.</department_description><detailed_description>The Project Coordinator will work closely with the study Principal Investigator (PI) to advance the work in close collaboration with the site PIs and their stakeholders. The group will develop consensus on many aspects of the work before the build and evaluation so those phases can unfold effectively. Responsibilities include planning projects and corresponding logistics, creating slide decks, coordinating bi-weekly project webinar meetings nationally, implementing demonstration project objectives locally, collecting evaluation data through surveys and other metrics, tracking on-time deliverables, and problem-solving directly with the PI. Additionally, PC will help with communications, such as maintaining the project webpage and will contribute to drafting project updates, progress reports, manuscripts, and presentations. Will assist PI in engaging study partners at collaborating sites maintaining effective communication, and sustaining partnership w/PIs, project managers, and other stakeholders.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s Degree required; Must have a minimum of three years of relevant experience. Project management for multi-site project coordination required; experience in qualitative research, health care research, or application development preferred. Proficiency in Microsoft Office, excellent organizational, written, and oral communication skills, and excellent interpersonal skills necessary. Must have excellent critical thinking and basic data analysis skills, work well with teams, and be detail-oriented and milestone/deadline-driven. Must be able to organize logistics for multi-site projects, have knowledge of REDCap, and proficiency in hosting webinars.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27533</id><title>Facility Operations Supervisor</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27533&amp;p_spid=1100136</url><publish_date>14-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Comparative Bioscience Center</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Veterinary Services</professional_area><department_description>The Comparative Bioscience Center provides a comprehensive program of animal care in support of the University&apos;s in vivo research. The goal of our staff is to provide investigators with the highest level of research support at the lowest cost while ensuring the welfare of the animals used in the research. The center is fully accredited by the Association for Assessment and Accreditation of Laboratory Animal Care International (AAALAC).</department_description><detailed_description>Under the supervision of the Associate Director of Facilities and the Facility Manager along with the assistance of two operations leads, will provide leadership while overseeing all segments of the Cage Wash, Porter, and Waste Management areas and personnel of the Comparative Bioscience Center (CBC). Responsibilities include planning, prioritizing, assigning, supervising, reviewing, and participating in the work of the staff responsible for facility operations; establishing schedules and methods for providing facility operations services, identifying resource needs, and reviewing needs with appropriate management of staff while allocating resources accordingly;  monitoring and controlling area supplies and equipment; developing and maintaining the Preventative Maintenance Schedule program for applicable equipment and machinery throughout the facility; arranging for and managing appropriate third-party contractor support as needed; ensuring that waste generated by the facility is managed following University policy, including generic and hazardous waste management duties; and ensuring that each employee involved in hazardous waste management performs their duties in compliance with proper hazardous waste handling and management procedures.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Associates degree or higher required and certification at the Laboratory Animal Technician (AALAS) level required. Previous experience in a large animal facility or university setting desired. Must have supervisory experience and be computer proficient. Must have strong written and verbal communication skills, excellent interpersonal skills, and be flexible and capable of adapting to a continuously changing and dynamic work environment. Must be comfortable working around various animal species housed in the university. Familiarity with the use, repair, and maintenance of machinery, including but not limited to rack and tunnel washers, autoclaves, bedding dispensers, caging equipment, mechanical floor cleaners, and electric tools used for repairs such as drills necessary. Familiarity with HVAC, plumbing, sanitation, and electric is a plus.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27555</id><title>Research Support Specialist</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27555&amp;p_spid=1101138</url><publish_date>19-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>High Throughput Screening Resource Center</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>&lt;p&gt;The High-Throughput and Spectroscopy Resource Center (HTSRC) supports scientists in the screening and identification of compounds and genetic modulators of in vitro assays which utilize optical and other bio-analytical technologies. High-Throughput Screening (HTS) requires the miniaturization and automation of bioassays so that millions of variables can be tested. HTS is often an important step in the discovery of new medicines. The center has a collection of over 380,000 compounds, automated liquid transfer devices, compound databases, and supports a broad diversity of assay development techniques, typically found in early drug discovery programs. The Center is configured for processing 96, 384 and 1536-well microtiter plates through the use of automated changeable tip dispensers, non-contact dispensers, and syringe dispensers. For assay technologies, the HTSRC has the capability to support cellular and biochemical assays using absorbance, fluorescent kinetics, fluorescence anisotropy, time-resolved fluorescence, time-resolved fluorescence resonance energy transfer, AlphaScreen, bioluminescence, for example luciferase and green fluorescent protein, scintillation proximity and cellular fluorescence imaging. Assay targets can include ion channels, receptors, enzymes, protein interactions, signaling pathways and cellular processes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The High-Throughput and Spectroscopy Resource Center also oversees the management of, training for, and scheduling for optical spectroscopic and calorimetric equipment for use in studies of the structure, function and interactions of biological and organic molecules. This includes an on-campus facility for nuclear magnetic resonance spectroscopy with priority access given to University researchers. The Center offers extensive training in basic and advanced NMR experiments and also coordinates access to high field spectrometers (700, 800, and 900 MHz) at the New York Structural Biology Center through the University&apos;s partnership in that Center. HTSRC staff provides general background training in applications of NMR spectroscopy to structural biology and chemistry and hands on training on the spectrometers. Trained users have 24/7 access to these instruments. Occasional users of the facilities may have spectra produced for them.&lt;/p&gt;</department_description><detailed_description>The Research Support Specialist will design, implement, and interpret experiments using novel and complex bioassay techniques supporting Rockefeller and Weil Cornell Medical College (WCMC) faculty, students, and post-docs. Will be responsible for management and maintenance of high throughput screening instruments and automated liquid handling, providing guidance of junior staff, organizing service contracts, repairs and troubleshooting, and oversight of vendor support. Will evaluate new technologies and provide analysis of new technologies, organize user groups and scientific information meetings, write sections of academic publications and reports, and represent the Center in public forums. Will report budgetary issues, personnel, and complex technical issues to the Director, but can function autonomously in the technical and scientific responsibilities. Additionally, as needed, can support and guide biophysical experiments towards the measurement of biomolecular interactions. May conduct an HTS project from novel assay development through confirmed hit list and preliminary SAR by inventory.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Ph.D. in a biochemistry-related discipline with significant postdoctoral biology experience and a minimum of five years of experience in an HTS-related setting with significant publication history required. Expert technical knowledge of the development of HTS assays involving various biochemical and cell-based technologies and practical understanding of chemical lead discovery necessary. Must have a proven ability to work collaboratively with users, be detail-oriented, and have high-priority management skills. Excellent communication and team-building skills are required. Mastery of techniques, including measuring cellular and enzyme/receptor systems, is necessary. Must be able to set and keep appropriate priorities.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27494</id><title>Research Support Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27494&amp;p_spid=1098137</url><publish_date>11-Jan-2022</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Genomics Resource Center</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>The Genomics Resource Center (GRC) provides a suite of platforms for supporting genomics research, including deep DNA sequencing using Illumina platforms (HiSeq 2500, NextSeq 500, and MiSeq), Gene Expression Analysis, SNP Genotyping, and Chromosomal Copy Number Variant Analysis using Affymetrix GeneChips; Single-cell Analysis with 10X Genomics Chromium system, individual gene expression and genotyping using realtime PCR, and sample prep and quality control instruments and assistance. The GRC provides support to both University and non-University researchers, with consistent usage by over 50 of the University&apos;s Laboratories. The GRC is dedicated to providing state-of-the-art technology, technical support and scientific consulting in the fast evolving field of genomics.</department_description><detailed_description>The Research Support Assistant will work as part of a team supporting the Rockefeller University community for genomics research. Responsibilities include preparing samples for next-generation sequencing, setting-up sequencers, maintaining instruments, interacting with users to receive samples, and performing sample quality and quantity checks, and troubleshooting with users and instrument companies. #INDRES21</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required; Master&apos;s degree preferred. Must have experience with molecular biology techniques. Experience with genomics technologies preferred. Must be versatile in instrumentation, with a strong sense of responsibility, and able to work as part of a team in a fast-paced environment. Strong attention to detail, interpersonal and communication skills are required. Computer proficiency necessary.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27493</id><title>Senior Research Support Specialist</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27493&amp;p_spid=1098136</url><publish_date>11-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Flow Cytometry Resource Center</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>The Flow Cytometry Resource Center (FCRC) offers a wide variety of multi-laser/multi-color flow cytometry sorters and analyzers, including spectral and imaging flow cytometers. The FCRC staff provide assistance with experimental design, advice on sample preparation, instrument operation training, troubleshooting, and data analysis consultation as well as ongoing instrument maintenance. High-speed cell sorting is performed by FCRC staff. However, after completing appropriate training, researchers can independently operate benchtop analyzers. The FCRC has three BD FACSArias, an ImageStream-X, a Cytek Aurora, a BD LSR-Fortessa and two BD LSRIIs, a ThermoFisher Attune NxT, and a BD Accuri C6.</department_description><detailed_description>The Senior Research Support Specialist will work in direct support of and collaboration with the Flow Cytometry Resource Center (FCRC) Director on technical and scientific tasks and initiatives, including but not limited to commissioning of new instrumentation; development, testing and implementation of new methods and protocols for quality control, tracking and standardization of the instruments; consultation, development and troubleshooting on multicolor panel and experimental design; and implementation of educational programs and development of new training materials.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The Senior Research Support Specialist will guide FCRC users through projects to ensure they are conducted in line with experimental plans, assisting with data verification, progress review, and data analysis. Will serve as the lead for developing and ensuring high standards for comprehensive flow cytometry data analysis for FCRC users, develop and implement FCRC training program for comprehensive data analysis, identify and establish relationships with relevant software vendors, provide technical and scientific support for flow cytometry software and collaborate with the Rockefeller University Bioinformatics Resource Center. The Senior Research Support Specialist will participate in daily FCRC operations, including performing advanced equipment troubleshooting, providing technical support in instrument set-up and operation, running routine cell-sorting experiments, and performing maintenance of the Center&apos;s scientific equipment. Will provide backup for the FCRC Operations Manager and/or Director as needed by managing booking confirmations and cancellations for cell sorting via the FCRC-PPMS system, learning in-depth capabilities of the FCRC-DB (database), processing invoices, and tracking equipment/supply ordering. The Senior Research Support Specialist will undertake professional development by attending and participating in training courses, webinars, seminars, funding opportunities, meetings, and conferences.&lt;/div&gt;</detailed_description><job_requirements>Master&apos;s degree in biology or related field required; Ph.D. strongly preferred. Educational background and experience in immunology are preferred. Must have a minimum of 3 years of experience in basic research-oriented flow cytometry, and a minimum of five concurrent or additional years of laboratory experience working with cell cultures and cells ex vivo. Competency with cell sorting is highly desirable. Must be able to work independently and meet responsibilities with very limited to no supervision. Multi-tasking is an essential skill. Excellent communication skills and ability to interact successfully with a broad range of individuals within and outside of the University required. Computer competency in both PC and MAC systems, as well as competency in relevant software programs required.</job_requirements><additional_details>Must be able and willing to work flexible/staggered shifts. (Full time, Monday-Friday). Ability to wear particulate filter respirator or powered air-purifying respirator required.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.&lt;/div&gt;</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC26789</id><title>Research Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=26789&amp;p_spid=1065092</url><publish_date>19-Aug-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Chemistry and Cell Biology</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>We study molecular mechanisms required for the stable propagation of our genomes with the goal of developing new therapies to treat cancer.  Errors in cell division have been linked to diseases and developmental defects in humans. We combine the discovery and use of chemical probes, synthetic chemistry, biochemistry, biophysics and quantitative cell biology to answer long-standing questions relating to cell division. Studying cell division also provides us an opportunity to develop new approaches for the analysis of other complex cellular mechanisms</department_description><detailed_description>Research Assistant, Chemistry and Cell Biology: Supervised by a senior scientist, the Research Assistant will work on a team project focusing on chemical biology using chemical synthesis, cell culture, protein purification, and various biochemical assays. Will learn and be responsible for cell culture, including generating, organizing, and managing several different cell lines and performing molecular biology techniques, including preparation of recombinant DNA and multi-step cloning to generate constructs. Responsibilities will also include ordering and distributing research supplies and maintaining inventories.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required; educational emphasis in molecular biology, cell biology, or biochemistry preferred. Previous laboratory experience in cell culture and molecular biology is preferred. Must have the ability to work effectively as part of a dynamic team to reach challenging milestones promptly and the ability to work independently with minimal supervision.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment.  Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27095</id><title>Animal Technician</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27095&amp;p_spid=1080098</url><publish_date>08-Oct-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Integrative Neuroscience</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>We are a group of physicists looking at living beings as a source of inspiration to create new mathematical descriptions of nature. We try to model their complexity, organization and self-assembling properties to answer the following questions: How can imprecise and noisy molecular machinery perform accurate tasks? How can the brain make complex and accurate computations using unreliable neurons?</department_description><detailed_description>The Integrative Neuroscience Laboratory is looking for an animal technician to join our team. Will oversee all aspects of life support, water quality control, and animal care for a small cephalopod operation and support the design and implementation of future expansions.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required; Bachelor&apos;s degree and educational emphasis in biology, chemistry, or the life sciences preferred. Must be interested in and enthusiastic about working Cephalopods. Previous experience working with Cephalopods preferred. Must be able to manage water quality and assist in future expansion design and implementation. Excellent organization skills to handle multiple tasks at once, and strong written and oral communication skills required. Must be enthusiastic about learning, a team player, and have strong commitment and responsibility. Must have the ability to anticipate and execute beyond given tasks and responsibilities. The successful candidate must have extensive experience setting up and maintaining salt-water aquaria and marine life.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment.  Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27554</id><title>Research Support Aide</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27554&amp;p_spid=1101137</url><publish_date>19-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Glasswashing Services</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Administrative and Support Services</professional_area><department_description></department_description><detailed_description>The Research Support Aide will be responsible for picking up and delivering glassware on time to various labs in multiple locations on campus. Will prepare items for sterilization, including proper packing and labeling, and operate glass washers, dryers, ovens, and sterilizers, paying attention to preset time and temperature settings for various items. Must assist with daily communication with customers, including troubleshooting to address concerns or questions related to job responsibilities, documenting customer requests and responding as needed, mailing and handling packages, and requesting reordering of supplies. Will maintain the cleanliness of workstations and equipment and daily and weekly restocking of supplies.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School Diploma or equivalent required. A minimum of one year of experience in a laboratory setting is highly preferred. Excellent spoken and written communication skills, and proficient computer software skills necessary. Must be able to maintain scheduled work hours (typically 8am to 4pm or similar) and work as a cohesive team.</job_requirements><additional_details>Ability to stand and walk for extended periods of time. Repetitive motion with arms and hands required to operate equipment. Ability to lift items up to 40 pounds.  Possible contact with hot working surfaces, acidic and basic detergents, and broken glassware.  This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC25678</id><title>Bioinformatics Assistant, Molecular Immunology</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=25678&amp;p_spid=1016039</url><publish_date>25-Jan-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Molecular Immunology</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>We pursue a combination of biochemical, molecular and genetic approaches to define the checkpoints that regulate B cell development, antibody production and B cell tolerance. A second area of interest is in dendritic cells. Our interests range from the earliest phases of the B cell pathway, including the commitment to becoming a B cell through the completion of maturation. Our ongoing work includes a focus on mechanisms of V(D)J recombination, somatic mutation, isotype switching, allelic exclusion and tolerance.</department_description><detailed_description>The Bioinformatics Assistant will join a team of researchers using a combination of biochemical, molecular, and genetic approaches to define the checkpoints that regulate B cell development, antibody production, and B cell tolerance, and study dendritic cells. Will also contribute to ongoing work on mechanisms of V(D)J recombination, somatic mutation, isotype switching, and allelic exclusion tolerance. The Bioinformatics Assistant will be responsible for maintaining the existing server infrastructure of the laboratory in collaboration with our IT department, maintaining the existing analysis pipelines, and continually identifying novel tools and annotation databases to improve the efficiency, sensitivity, and functionality of the results.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in computational biology, computer science, biological sciences, or other related analytical discipline required. Must have excellent programming skills in at least one scripting language such as Perl, Python, or R, and knowledge of SQL. Must be comfortable working in a Unix/Linux operating system, know command-line tools, the ability to multitask while working independently and exercising good judgement in terms of meeting deadlines, the ability to maintain well documented and tested code, and the ability to thoroughly document analysis results. Must be motivated to learn new technologies, contribute towards publications in peer-reviewed journals, and have strong communication skills with the ability to interact with other researchers from diverse scientific backgrounds. Must have experience in scientific programming with applications to biomedical research, preferably in the area of genomics and next-generation sequencing analysis.
 </job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment.  Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27562</id><title>Research Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27562&amp;p_spid=1101145</url><publish_date>20-Jan-2022</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Biochemistry and Molecular Biology</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>The processes of animal cell growth, differentiation and infection by viruses result from the differential expression of specific genes, controlled primarily at the level of transcription. Our broad objectives are to understand the specific regulatory events that control these processes, as well as more fundamental aspects of transcription activation and repression mechanisms. To this end, our specific objectives are to determine the nature and mechanism of action of both the general transcription initiation factors that are commonly used by all genes and the gene- and cell type-specific factors that directly regulate target genes in response to various growth, developmental and viral stimuli. Our experimental strategy has been (1) to reconstitute cell-free systems in which cloned genes, as free DNA or after assembly into chromatin, are accurately transcribed by general factors and regulated by gene-specific factors, (2) to dissect biochemically these systems and to purify and clone the individual factors and (3) to study the structure, function and regulation of these factors by a combination of biochemical and genetic (e.g., transgenic and knockout mice) analyses.</department_description><detailed_description>We seek a talented Research Assistant to work under the general direction of senior research staff and conduct activities to support research projects in the fields of biochemistry and molecular and cell biology. The Research Assistant will perform day-to-day experimental activities, in addition to the maintenance of general laboratory functions. Will monitor laboratory and/or other supplies to ensure sufficient inventory to support research projects and ensure the quality of reagents or other supplies.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree required; Master&apos;s degree preferred. Must have experience in biochemistry and molecular and cell biology and a minimum of two years of experience in cloning/recombinant DNA technology, recombinant protein expression (mammalian, baculovirus, and bacterial vectors) and purification (affinity and ion-exchange chromatography), in vitro and cell-based transcription assays, and cell culture.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC26868</id><title>Research Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=26868&amp;p_spid=1069091</url><publish_date>03-Sep-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Cellular Biophysics</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>We study the organization of cells, with a particular emphasis on the mechanisms that control the compartmentalization of cellular components. We study the principles that govern how macromolecules cross membranes or are integrated into membranes, the physiological and pathological consequences of (im)proper compartmentalization, and develop new technologies for studying cellular function.</department_description><detailed_description>The Research Assistant will assist in developing therapeutics for cancers that affect adolescents and young adults, generating mouse models for these cancers. Will be responsible for caring for and maintaining multiple mice colonies and propagating human tumors in mice. The Research Assistant will manage mice injected with tumor samples collected from patients and mice engineered to have the drivers for cancer. The Research Assistant will keep a record of all changes with mice (weight gain/loss, temperament, comfortability, etc.).</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required.  Must be comfortable working with mice. Must be able to multi-task, have excellent communication, record keeping, and organizational skills, and be computer literate. Must be reliable and detail-oriented.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment.  Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC26829</id><title>Research Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=26829&amp;p_spid=1067092</url><publish_date>24-Aug-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Developmental Genetics</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>Apoptosis (programmed cell death) is essential for metazoan development. We study apoptosis in the nematode C. elegans, and are interested in understanding cues that regulate apoptosis during development. To this end we have used genetic strategies to identify cell-specific apoptosis regulators. The remarkable conservation of the apoptotic machinery suggests that our studies will yield insight into the regulation of mammalian apoptosis. Glia account for 90 percent of the cells in the human brain, yet compared to their neuronal counterparts little is known about their development, function and morphogenesis. C. elegans contains 24 neuron-associated cells that are strikingly similar to vertebrate glia. We are interested in understanding how these cells develop, acquire their morphologies and regulate neuronal activity. We are using laser ablation, time-lapse microscopy, genomic and genetic approaches to address these issues.</department_description><detailed_description>Under the mentorship of a Postdoctoral Scholar, the Research Assistant will contribute to ongoing projects within the Laboratory.  Responsibilities include genetic crosses, genotyping (PCR, agarose gel electrophoresis, DNA sequence analysis), creating transgenic C. elegans strains (including DNA cloning), and analyzing gene expression using fluorescence microscopy and image analysis.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required; educational emphasis in genetics and cell biology preferred. Prior research with C. elegans is a plus. Candidates with experience in genetics, molecular biology, and fluorescence microscopy are especially encouraged to apply. Must be highly motivated and driven by scientific curiosity, possess excellent verbal, written, and electronic communication skills, and the ability to interact effectively in a collaborative work environment. Must have excellent organizational skills, including laboratory record keeping, data management, and prioritizing work to carry out complex experiments with extreme attention to detail. Previous independent research experience or extensive laboratory coursework is strongly preferred.  Must be amenable to changing work schedules that prioritize experiments and which often deviate from the standard 9 to 5 workday, occasionally including weekend hours.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment.  Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27492</id><title>Research Support Specialist</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27492&amp;p_spid=1098135</url><publish_date>11-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Proteomics Resource Center</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>&lt;p&gt;The Proteomics Resource Center at The Rockefeller University masters most aspects of mass spectrometry based proteomics which includes, denovo sequencing, targeted studies, quantitative proteomics profiling based on label free quantitation as well as metabolic labelled samples (SILAC), chemical labeling, tandem-mass tag technology, absolute quantitation and global post translational analysis. The Center also offers LC-MS based analysis of small molecules, polar metabolites and lipids. Very importantly, the Center is a source for help with planning of mass spectrometry based experiments and the Center have the capability to offer in-depth collaborative analysis. Also, the PRC is operated in a boutique style; encouraging the scientists of the Center to work closely with users to create a tailored approach to fit the many unique questions that can be answered by analytical mass spectrometry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The PRC are equipped with Orbitrap type mass spectrometers (high resolution/high mass accuracy), operates a triple quadrupole and can separate analytes using both nano and high flow liquid chromatography. The Center is equipped with multiple high performance servers for data analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to analysis by mass spectrometry, the Center offers production of custom peptides and peptide libraries and different pre-mass spectrometry fractionation techniques, which include off-line separation of peptides and proteins by liquid chromatography.&lt;/p&gt;</department_description><detailed_description>The Research Support Associate will apply mass spectrometry-based analytical chemistry to exciting projects, spanning a wide range of samples and project types. Reporting to the Director of the PRC, responsibilities include maintaining and operating nano and high-flow LC coupled to Orbitrap mass spectrometers and related equipment, interacting with and advising investigators about experiments, developing and implementing protocols in the Center, processing, analyzing, and interpreting data and reporting findings to investigators and the Director, tracking and submitting billing and purchasing information, and monitoring and maintaining laboratory appearance. #INDRES21</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree required; educational emphasis in science-related fields, biology and chemistry preferred. Must have strong analytical and practical skills in sample preparation and data analysis and interpretation, excellent communication skills in oral and written English, the ability to work independently as well as part of a team, and flexibility to interact with a diverse group of researchers. Hands-on experience with liquid chromatography and mass spectrometry required. Must have experience in documenting experiments and maintaining and expanding knowledge of mass spectrometry techniques through self-education, dialog with experts, reading literature, and attending conferences and courses as necessary. Practical experience with informatics is desirable.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27449</id><title>Supervisor of Glasswashing Services</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27449&amp;p_spid=1096132</url><publish_date>17-Dec-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Glassware Resource Center</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Administrative and Support Services</professional_area><department_description>Glasswashing Services provides University Laboratories with high quality, efficient washing, baking, and autoclaving of laboratory glassware - a service that is essential to the conduct of the University&apos;s research. Glasswashing Services also manages third-party pipette calibration, ensuring timely and less expensive services for the Laboratories. The facility provides pick-up and delivery directly to the laboratory, generally as a same day service. Services include washing, drying, baking, sterilization, pipette plugging, and autoclaving of liquids. Glasswashing Services is available for regular, ongoing glasswashing services as well as provision of temporary and emergency backup services for Laboratories when their staff is on vacation or equipment is down for servicing.</department_description><detailed_description>Reporting to the Associate Vice President for Research Support, will be responsible for the oversight and management of the operations and staff of the Glasswashing Services. This centralized core facility provides essential glasswashing and autoclaving services and other complementary or related services directly to the Laboratories. Will be responsible for hands-on involvement in glasswashing services, ensuring staff performance, and the department&apos;s overall operation in adherence to departmental and University policies and procedures. Will be responsible for annual performance reviews of the team, preparation of and adherence to the yearly operating budget, ordering department supplies, staff uniforms, and equipment parts, tracking service levels, implementing a billing system, and the monthly submission of billing information to finance.  Will be responsible for the oversight of contracted pipette calibration services and coordination with laboratories for centralized provision of this service on a charge-back basis, troubleshooting facility equipment, identifying new equipment needs and facilitating installation and commissioning, problem-solving with users, vendors, and representatives from other University service departments, preparing reports on department operations for review by the administration as needed, recruitment and training of new staff members, and developing and facilitating new avenues of facility service.  During phase III and III+ COVID operations, will be the lead for distribution and collection of RUStrong kits and samples, including regular coordination with the RUStrong team and RROs.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree or equivalent work experience required.  Previous supervisory experience and laboratory or technical experience are necessary.  Must be responsible, have strong attention to detail, and excellent interpersonal and customer service skills for daily interaction with all levels of University personnel.  Familiarity with the types of instrumentation in the facility and competency with best practices for laboratory glassware washing and sterilization necessary.  Proficiency in basic PC skills including Microsoft Office suite, email, internet required; Familiarity with Oracle-based HR and Procurement modules a plus.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC25966</id><title>Carpenter Helper</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=25966&amp;p_spid=1029048</url><publish_date>22-Mar-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Plant Operations</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Building and Grounds Maintenance</professional_area><department_description>Plant Operations offers comprehensive services at The Rockefeller University including a full range of building trades services which are responsible for routine maintenance and minor/major space alterations, plumbing, electrical, carpentry, HVAC, grounds maintenance, locksmith, custodial, moving and setup services.</department_description><detailed_description>Reporting to the Supervisor of the Carpenter Shop, the Carpenter Helper will install and repair acoustic ceilings, drywall, doors, door and window frames, and hardware. Will also handle fabrication of phenolic benchtops, lath and plaster walls and ceilings, and install cabinetry, furniture, and ceramic tile. Responsibilities also include cleaning and protection of work areas for carpentry shop and other trades, picking up deliveries, and stocking materials.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required. Must have a minimum of 2-3 years of relevant experience. Knowledge of power and hand tools required. Must be able and willing to work in all conditions (inside, outside, all weather conditions, etc). Some construction background necessary.</job_requirements><additional_details>Must be able to climb extension ladders, work overhead, and balance, stoop, kneel, crouch, and move within confined areas including crawl and attic spaces. Must be able to sustain considerable physical effort at frequent intervals. Must be able to move, push, pull, or lift equipment, materials, and tools weighing 80 lbs.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment.  Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.&lt;/div&gt;</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27356</id><title>Mechanic II</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27356&amp;p_spid=1092119</url><publish_date>19-Nov-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Plant Operations HVAC Shop</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Building and Grounds Maintenance</professional_area><department_description>Plant Operations offers comprehensive services at The Rockefeller University including a full range of building trades services which are responsible for routine maintenance and minor/major space alterations, plumbing, electrical, carpentry, HVAC, grounds maintenance, locksmith, custodial, moving and setup services.</department_description><detailed_description>Working as part of the HVAC shop in Plant Operations, the Refrigeration Helper will troubleshoot and repair all refrigeration systems, including cold rooms, ice machines, DX units, domestic refrigerators, and freezers.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required; some trade school and EPA refrigeration handling certification preferred. Must be able to follow instructions and learn to braze and solder. Previous experience with electrical, plumbing, mechanical, and HVAC and good mechanical and diagnostics skills preferred. Must have good communication skills, motor coordination, and have good dexterity.</job_requirements><additional_details>Must be able to work in confined spaces and elevated temperatures, meet established attendance standards, and have the ability to work on ladders, scaffolds, and to sit, stand, and walk for momentary to extended periods of time. Must have the ability to work safely with hazardous materials. Will be required to work as necessary during disaster situations (before, during, or after a disaster) and may be required to stay after workday to assist after a disaster situation until relief arrives. Must be able to move, push, pull, or lift equipment, materials, and tools weighing more than 50 lbs., climb extension ladders, work overhead, and balance, stoop, kneel, crouch, and move within confined areas including crawl and attic spaces. Must be able to sustain considerable physical effort at frequent intervals, work both inside and outside, and operate power tools and equipment. Will be required to work evenings, weekends, and holidays when necessary.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.&lt;/div&gt;</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC26256</id><title>Mechanic I</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=26256&amp;p_spid=1042058</url><publish_date>10-May-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Plant Operations</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Building and Grounds Maintenance</professional_area><department_description>Plant Operations offers comprehensive services at The Rockefeller University including a full range of building trades services which are responsible for routine maintenance and minor/major space alterations, plumbing, electrical, carpentry, HVAC, grounds maintenance, locksmith, custodial, moving and setup services.</department_description><detailed_description>Under general direction, the mechanic will perform semi-skilled and skilled work in the operation, maintenance, and repair of heating, ventilation, refrigeration, and air conditioning systems. The Mechanic I will be responsible for using mechanical skills to repair piping and ductwork and changing motor bearings and pump seals. Responsibilities include repairing and maintaining boilers, pipes, thermostats, air filters, pumps, waste and oil pressure indicators, blower fans, belts, and bearings, operating computerized heating and cooling equipment for large, complex systems at centralized and decentralized building plants, and troubleshooting, diagnosing, repairing, and reprogramming electric, electronic, and pneumatic controls of buildings by reading schematics and using computer energy management software. Will lead and/or instruct building maintenance workers in the performance of routine maintenance of HVAC equipment, design and install new small to medium-sized HVAC systems, perform data entry related to preventative maintenance, and calculate the amount of Freon to be used in air conditioning systems.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required. Must have a minimum of three to five years of journey-level experience operating, maintaining, and repairing ventilating and air conditioning equipment or a combination of training, education, and experience equivalent to the employment standard listed above. Must be able to read blueprints and operating manuals, troubleshoot and solve HVAC/R problems, understand electric and building management systems such as Siemens, Honeywell, and Auto-Matrix, and be able to soft solder and braze as well as charge and recover refrigerants from different systems such as EPA type 1 recovery.</job_requirements><additional_details>Must be able to work in confined spaces and elevated temperatures, meet established attendance standards, work on ladders, scaffolds, and sit, stand, and walk for momentary to extended periods. Must have the ability to work safely with hazardous materials. Will be required to work as necessary during disaster situations (before, during, or after a disaster) and may be required to stay after workday to assist after a disaster situation until relief arrives. Must be able to move, push, pull, or lift equipment, materials, and tools weighing more than 50 lbs., climb extension ladders, work overhead, and balance, stoop, kneel, crouch, and move within confined areas, including crawl and attic spaces. Must be able to sustain considerable physical effort at frequent intervals, work both inside and outside, and operate power tools and equipment. Will be required to work evenings, weekends, and holidays when necessary.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment.  Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.&lt;/div&gt;</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27452</id><title>Mechanic, Power House (3 PM to 11 PM)</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27452&amp;p_spid=1096135</url><publish_date>21-Dec-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Plant Operations Power House</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Engineering (Power Plant)</professional_area><department_description>Plant Operations offers comprehensive services at The Rockefeller University including a full range of building trades services which are responsible for routine maintenance and minor/major space alterations, plumbing, electrical, carpentry, HVAC, grounds maintenance, locksmith, custodial, moving and setup services.</department_description><detailed_description>Under the supervision of Engineering Management and the Lead Mechanic, the Mechanic will operate and maintain the physical plant and University buildings to ensure a safe and efficient environment and to continually work towards and support the improvement of engineering services. Supervision of the 3 pm- 11 pm shift will be under the direction of the Watch Engineer and Maintenance Engineer. Will provide technical and general preventative maintenance and repair for a wide range of equipment and utility systems, including but not limited to: boilers and their auxiliaries, plumbing, electrical, HVAC, also including air handlers, domestic water, chilled water, hot water, steam, building exhaust, compressed air, controls, lighting, fire systems, etc. The Mechanic will maintain constant attention to the overall operations of the physical plant and University buildings, keep accurate records of temperatures, loads, steam pressure, steam flow, and water analysis, and read and interpret readings from meters and gauges and other measuring units. Additional responsibilities include completing all work safely and professionally, responding to emergency calls for system or equipment failures, and assisting other maintenance and engineering personnel when necessary. Will perform additional duties requested by the Chief/Assistant Chief Engineer and Watch Engineer to ensure the effective operation of the physical plant and University buildings.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required; Trade School graduate or current New York City Stationary Refrigeration License preferred. Three years of experience will be credited for an NYC Refrigeration License. Must have a minimum of three years of work experience in power plant operations and preventative maintenance, including boilers, plumbing, electrical, and HVAC equipment. Must be able to read and interpret diagrams, blueprints, and equipment manuals. Technical and general preventative maintenance experience and repair for a wide range of equipment and utility systems necessary; experience with absorption/centrifugal chillers and process chillers preferred, and a utility plant systems and operations background desired. Must be familiar with lubrication and other corrective and preventative maintenance for needed repairs. Must be able to read, write, and communicate effectively with individuals at all levels inside and outside the department. Excellent organization skills and the ability to learn new tasks, prioritize and organize work assignments, and work under stressful situations with good judgment required. Must be available for any emergencies and act in an engineering capacity to protect and preserve the physical plant and University buildings and their systems during an emergency. Schedule rotation may be required.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs. Schedule rotation may be required.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27455</id><title>Mechanic, Power House (7 AM to 3 PM)</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27455&amp;p_spid=1096138</url><publish_date>21-Dec-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Plant Operations Power House</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Building and Grounds Maintenance</professional_area><department_description>Plant Operations offers comprehensive services at The Rockefeller University including a full range of building trades services which are responsible for routine maintenance and minor/major space alterations, plumbing, electrical, carpentry, HVAC, grounds maintenance, locksmith, custodial, moving and setup services.</department_description><detailed_description>Under the supervision of Engineering Management and the Lead Mechanic, the Mechanic will operate and maintain the physical plant and University buildings to ensure a safe and efficient environment and to continually work towards and support the improvement of engineering services. Supervision of the 7 AM - 3 PM shift will be under the direction of the Watch Engineer and Maintenance Engineer. Will provide technical and general preventative maintenance and repair for a wide range of equipment and utility systems, including but not limited to: boilers and their auxiliaries, plumbing, electrical, HVAC, also including air handlers, domestic water, chilled water, hot water, steam, building exhaust, compressed air, controls, lighting, fire systems, etc. The Mechanic will maintain constant attention to the overall operations of the physical plant and University buildings, keep accurate records of temperatures, loads, steam pressure, steam flow, and water analysis, and read and interpret readings from meters and gauges and other measuring units. Additional responsibilities include completing all work safely and professionally, responding to emergency calls for system or equipment failures, and assisting other maintenance and engineering personnel when necessary. Will perform additional duties requested by the Chief/Assistant Chief Engineer and Watch Engineer to ensure the effective operation of the physical plant and University buildings.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required; Trade School graduate or current New York City Stationary Refrigeration License preferred. Three years of experience will be credited for an NYC Refrigeration License. Must have a minimum of three years of work experience in power plant operations and preventative maintenance, including boilers, plumbing, electrical, and HVAC equipment. Must be able to read and interpret diagrams, blueprints, and equipment manuals. Technical and general preventative maintenance experience and repair for a wide range of equipment and utility systems necessary; experience with absorption/centrifugal chillers and process chillers preferred, and a utility plant systems and operations background desired. Must be familiar with lubrication and other corrective and preventative maintenance for needed repairs. Must be able to read, write, and communicate effectively with individuals at all levels inside and outside the department. Excellent organization skills and the ability to learn new tasks, prioritize and organize work assignments, and work under stressful situations with good judgment required. Must be available for any emergencies and act in an engineering capacity to protect and preserve the physical plant and University buildings and their systems during an emergency. Schedule rotation may be required.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs. Schedule rotation may be required.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27334</id><title>Campus Security Officer</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27334&amp;p_spid=1091117</url><publish_date>18-Nov-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Security</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Security Services</professional_area><department_description>The Security Office is responsible for providing protection of all persons and property on campus.  We verify the identification of guests, visitors, and all University members, patrol and inspect the various campus buildings, respond to all emergencies on campus, and conduct investigations and prepare appropriate reports.</department_description><detailed_description>The Campus Security Officer will be responsible for providing protection of all persons and property, verifying the identification of guests, visitors, and all University members, providing information and directions, explaining rules and regulations, maintaining logs and records of occurrences, and completing necessary paperwork. Will also be responsible for patrolling and inspecting on foot the various campus buildings to ensure personal, building, and equipment security, responding to all emergencies on campus, as well as conducting investigations and preparing appropriate written reports of incidents, accidents, and crimes. May use the computer terminal to input and retrieve data.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required. Must be registered by the State of New York, Division of Licensing as a Security Guard, and have a New York State Driver&apos;s License. Must possess the F1/F3 Fire Guard License or obtain it within three months of employment. Three or more years of security experience required. Strong verbal and written communication skills in English necessary. Must have the ability to work under pressure, deal with people under stressful situations while maintaining composure, and be able to react and make sound decisions quickly in demanding conditions. Must be polite, courteous, and professional at all times, and ready to observe and recall situations and events. Must be able to understand and carry out complicated oral instructions. Must be willing and available to work weekends and overtime shifts. Prior police or military experience is a plus. Must be able to work from 6 am to 2:00 pm, Sunday through Thursday.Additional: Must be able to walk long distances, climb stairs, run short distances for emergency responses, and stand for long periods in all types of weather. A standard uniform is provided.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27101</id><title>Campus Security Officer (6 am - 2 pm, Sunday through Thursday)</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27101&amp;p_spid=1080104</url><publish_date>19-Oct-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Security</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Security Services</professional_area><department_description>The Security Office is responsible for providing protection of all persons and property on campus.  We verify the identification of guests, visitors, and all University members, patrol and inspect the various campus buildings, respond to all emergencies on campus, and conduct investigations and prepare appropriate reports.</department_description><detailed_description>The Campus Security Officer will be responsible for providing protection of all persons and property, verifying the identification of guests, visitors, and all University members, providing information and directions, explaining rules and regulations, maintaining logs and records of occurrences, and completing necessary paperwork. Will also be responsible for patrolling and inspecting on foot the various campus buildings to ensure personal, building, and equipment security, responding to all emergencies on campus, as well as conducting investigations and preparing appropriate written reports of incidents, accidents, and crimes. May use the computer terminal to input and retrieve data.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required. Must be registered by the State of New York, Division of Licensing as a Security Guard, and have a New York State Driver&apos;s License. Must possess the F1/F3 Fire Guard License or obtain it within three months of employment. Three or more years of security experience required. Strong verbal and written communication skills in English necessary. Must have the ability to work under pressure, deal with people under stressful situations while maintaining composure, and be able to react and make sound decisions quickly in demanding conditions. Must be polite, courteous, and professional at all times and ready to observe and recall situations and events. Must be able to understand and carry out complicated oral instructions. Must be willing and available to work weekends and overtime shifts. Prior police or military experience a plus. Must be able to work from 6 am to 2:00 pm, Sunday through Thursday.</job_requirements><additional_details>Must be able to walk long distances, climb stairs, run short distances for emergency responses, and stand for long periods in all types of weather. A standard uniform is provided.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.&lt;/div&gt;</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27552</id><title>Manager of Custodial Services</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27552&amp;p_spid=1101135</url><publish_date>19-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Plant Operations Custodial Services</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Waste Management Services</professional_area><department_description>Plant Operations offers comprehensive services at The Rockefeller University including a full range of building trades services which are responsible for routine maintenance and minor/major space alterations, plumbing, electrical, carpentry, HVAC, grounds maintenance, locksmith, custodial, moving and setup services.</department_description><detailed_description>Under the supervision of the Assistant Director of Plant Operations, the Manager of Custodial Services will manage a variety of cleaning personnel and tasks to maintain a safe and clean University Campus. Will Manage and direct all the snow removal, rubbish collection, and recycling program on campus. Will be responsible for the day-to-day operations of the Custodial Department, including scheduling daily work for the custodial staff, approving vacation requests, tracking employee attendance, maintaining stockroom supplies, and checking inventory levels once a week. Will assist the Assistant Director in preparing the Custodial budget, conducting yearly employee evaluations for the members of the day shift, and greeting and assisting all who come to the department. Will also assist all laboratories and departments in the coordination of any moves, including furniture moving and set up, and schedule deliveries as requested.  Will provide telephone coverage and assists Plant Operations personnel in answering calls as needed.  Will prepare service orders and issue them to the proper personnel, as well as handle the associated data entry. Will also coordinate and attend all required meetings with campus departments in facilitating conference and function setups in all areas on campus. Must oversee supply requests for custodians, and monitor requests for quantitative evaluation. Must handle petty cash and distribute accordingly. Will oversee event and project book for the day shift, daily sign-in sheets, and enter payroll sheets weekly.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required; higher degree preferred. Must have 5 years of supervisory experience in a hospital or academic environment. Excellent communication skills (oral and written English skills), and computer proficiency necessary, including Microsoft Suite (Word, Excel, Outlook).  Familiarity with quality assurance programs, regulations for the Environment of Care as set forth by the Joint Commission for Accreditation of Hospitals, and certification from either the International Executive Housekeepers Association or the American Society for Healthcare Environmental Services preferred. Must possess the ability and skills required to perform electronic computerized tasks needed to prepare reports.</job_requirements><additional_details>Perform medium to heavy lifting as assigned. Must be able to work with cleaning chemicals, lift at least 50 pounds, walk up and downstairs, and climb ladders. Must be able to bend and stoop over a lengthy period, must be able to distinguish colors, and have a full range of hand dexterity motion. May work odd hours and weekends in emergency situations. This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27561</id><title>Plumber</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27561&amp;p_spid=1101144</url><publish_date>20-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Plant Operations Office</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Building and Grounds Maintenance</professional_area><department_description>Plant Operations offers comprehensive services at The Rockefeller University including a full range of building trades services which are responsible for routine maintenance and minor/major space alterations, plumbing, electrical, carpentry, HVAC, grounds maintenance, locksmith, custodial, moving and setup services.</department_description><detailed_description>Under the supervision of the Foreman and officials responsible for the coordination and accomplishment of plant maintenance and operations work, the Plumber will be responsible for installing, repairing, and maintaining pipes, fixtures, and other plumbing used for water distribution and wastewater disposal in residential, commercial and industrial buildings. Must work safely and keep work area clean, maintaining and reviewing building plans and specifications to determine the layout of plumbing and materials. Must ensure all installations, repairs, and maintenance meet code requirements, testing pipe systems and fixtures. Must be willing to cross-trade, and maintain a valid driver&apos;s license with current insurance.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required. Journeyman Certification in Plumbing and 10 years of related experience necessary. Must have proficient knowledge in water distribution and wastewater disposal, and hoisting and rigging skills. Excellent analytical, problem-solving, and time management skills necessary. Strong computer skills, presentation, and written and verbal skills required. The ability to mentor fellow employees to enhance their skill sets necessary. May be required to operate power tools. Will be required to perform other duties as requested, directed or assigned.</job_requirements><additional_details>Will be required to lift, carry, push, and pull materials and equipment to and from the job site, some of which may weigh in excess of 50 pounds. Will be required to bend, stretch, kneel, crouch, crawl, and climb ladders to significant heights to inspect and repair pipes located in ceilings and walls. Must be able to stand or walk for long periods of time and be able to see naturally or with correction to safely perform designated tasks, including working under all types of environmental and weather conditions including severe cold, extreme heat, wet or dry weather, and high winds. Environmental conditions may include areas where toxic or caustics chemicals or fumes are in use or being stored.  This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27556</id><title>Plumber</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27556&amp;p_spid=1101139</url><publish_date>19-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Plant Operations Maintenance</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Building and Grounds Maintenance</professional_area><department_description>Plant Operations offers comprehensive services at The Rockefeller University including a full range of building trades services which are responsible for routine maintenance and minor/major space alterations, plumbing, electrical, carpentry, HVAC, grounds maintenance, locksmith, custodial, moving and setup services.</department_description><detailed_description>Under the supervision of the Foreman and officials responsible for the coordination and accomplishment of plant maintenance and operations work, the Plumber will be responsible for installing, repairing, and maintaining pipes, fixtures and other plumbing used for water distribution and wastewater disposal in residential, commercial and industrial buildings. Must work safely and keep work area clean, maintaining and reviewing building plans and specifications to determine the layout of plumbing and materials. Must ensure all installations, repairs, and maintenance meet code requirements, testing pipe systems and fixtures. Must be willing to cross-trade, and maintain a valid driver&apos;s license with current insurance.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required. Journeyman Certification in Plumbing and 10 years of related experience necessary. Must have proficient knowledge in water distribution and wastewater disposal, and hoisting and rigging skills. Excellent analytical, problem-solving, and time management skills necessary. Strong computer skills, presentation, and written and verbal skills required. The ability to mentor fellow employees to enhance their skill sets necessary. May be required to operate power tools. Will be required to perform other duties as requested, directed or assigned.</job_requirements><additional_details>Will be required to lift, carry, push, and pull materials and equipment to and from the job site, some of which may weigh in excess of 50 pounds. Will be required to bend, stretch, kneel, crouch, crawl, and climb ladders to significant heights to inspect and repair pipes located in ceilings and walls. Must be able to stand or walk for long periods of time and be able to see naturally or with correction to safely perform designated tasks, including working under all types of environmental and weather conditions including severe cold, extreme heat, wet or dry weather, and high winds. Environmental conditions may include areas where toxic or caustics chemicals or fumes are in use or being stored.  This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27514</id><title>Operations Analyst</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27514&amp;p_spid=1099137</url><publish_date>13-Jan-2022</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Investments</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Finance</professional_area><department_description>The Office of Investments oversees an endowment of $2.2 billion, broadly diversified across a range of asset classes. The primary role of the endowment is to advance the research mission of the University through support of the annual operating budget. Endowment assets are invested in public securities, including U.S. and non-U.S. equity and fixed income securities, and private investments including private equity, venture capital and real assets. The assets are invested by external investment managers through separate accounts or commingled vehicles, including funds, trusts and limited partnerships. In addition to overseeing the endowment, the Office of Investments plays an active role in planning and executing the University&apos;s external capital program including debt financings and interest rate swaps, and in maintaining the University&apos;s rating agency relationships. The University is rated Aa1/AA+ by Moody&apos;s and Standard and Poor&apos;s.  The current professional staff includes the Chief Investment Officer, Deputy Chief Investment Officer, and four additional investment professionals.</department_description><detailed_description>The Operations Analyst will provide general administrative support for the Office of Investments, including operations, analytical, and managerial support. The Operations Analyst reports to the Chief Investment Officer (CIO) and interacts with investment managers, service providers, and other departments in the University. Responsibilities include organizing and processing manager data, including monthly asset values and performance data for new and prospective investments, tracking liquidity terms for underlying investments and monitoring the endowment&apos;s overall liquidity, reconciling daily cash balances with capital calls, distributions, stock sales, gifts, and other flows, recording and tracking cash and stock distributions, and assisting with coding distributions for cost/gain, etc. The Operations Analyst will lead the process of quarterly reconciliations and serve as the primary contact for related inquiries between the Investments Office, Finance, and third-party vendors, collaborate with existing software providers to better utilize existing offerings, to encourage the development of new ones, and to ensure the accuracy of the data that sits on those platforms, assist with inquiries related to annual audits, filing of financial statements, and rating agency requests, build investment analytic capacity by centralizing key data collection of new and on-going investments, such as liquidity terms, holdings and performance details, and communications from fund managers, integrate and test operational systems to automate investment data collection, analysis, and reporting, monitor inbound communications, initiate related workflows and processes, and maintain the document management system, complete subscription packages and new account set-up for investments, and work with the team to prepare regular and ad hoc investment portfolio monitoring reports. #INDBIOINFO21</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree and a minimum of one year of work experience, preferably in accounting and investment operations, required. Must be adept at using computers and Microsoft Excel and be detail-oriented to solve complex problems and ensure data accuracy. Must be highly motivated with a willingness to learn and contribute to the team and work in a professional and confidential environment. Strong interpersonal and organizational skills, with the ability to balance multiple work streams and deadlines necessary. Must have the ability to work independently and autonomously. Experience as a CPA and experience with coding is preferred.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27377</id><title>Operations Analyst</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27377&amp;p_spid=1093120</url><publish_date>30-Nov-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Investments</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Finance</professional_area><department_description>The Office of Investments oversees an endowment of $2.9 billion, broadly diversified across a range of asset classes.  The primary role of the endowment is to advance the research mission of the University through the support of the annual operating budget.Endowment assets are invested in public securities, including U.S. and non-U.S. equity and fixed income securities, and private investments including private equity, venture capital, and real assets.  The assets are invested by external investment managers through separate accounts or commingled vehicles, including funds, trusts, and limited partnerships.  The current professional staff includes the Chief Investment Officer, one Senior Director, one Senior Investment Associate, and two Analysts. We are an academically rigorous, strategically focused, creatively balanced group built for the future. Come join us!</department_description><detailed_description>The Operations Analyst will provide general administrative support for the Office of Investments, including operations, analytical, and managerial support. The Operations Analyst reports to the Chief Investment Officer (CIO) and interacts with investment managers, service providers, and other departments in the University. Responsibilities include organizing and processing manager data, including monthly asset values and performance data for new and prospective investments, tracking liquidity terms for underlying investments and monitoring the endowment&apos;s overall liquidity, reconciling daily cash balances with capital calls, distributions, stock sales, gifts, and other flows, recording and tracking cash and stock distributions, and assisting with coding distributions for cost/gain, etc. The Operations Analyst will lead the process of quarterly reconciliations and serve as the primary contact for related inquiries between the Investments Office, Finance, and third-party vendors, collaborate with existing software providers to better utilize existing offerings, to encourage the development of new ones, and to ensure the accuracy of the data that sits on those platforms, assist with inquiries related to annual audits, filing of financial statements, and rating agency requests, build investment analytic capacity by centralizing key data collection of new and on-going investments, such as liquidity terms, holdings and performance details, and communications from fund managers, integrate and test operational systems to automate investment data collection, analysis, and reporting, monitor inbound communications, initiate related workflows and processes, and maintain the document management system, complete subscription packages and new account set-up for investments, and work with the team to prepare regular and ad hoc investment portfolio monitoring reports.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree and a minimum of one year of work experience, preferably in accounting and investment operations, required. Must be adept at using computers and Microsoft Excel and be detail-oriented to solve complex problems and ensure data accuracy. Must be highly motivated with a willingness to learn and contribute to the team and work in a professional and confidential environment.  Strong interpersonal and organizational skills, with the ability to balance multiple work streams and deadlines necessary. Must have the ability to work independently and autonomously. Experience as a CPA and experience with coding is preferred.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27450</id><title>Assistant Director, Treasury</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27450&amp;p_spid=1096133</url><publish_date>21-Dec-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Finance Accounting Services</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Finance</professional_area><department_description>The Finance Department of the University encompasses the Controller&apos;s Office and the Office of Budget, Treasury and Research Administration. These offices are dedicated to ensuring the integrity of data submitted, recorded and reported and to providing the highest level of financial services in support of the University&apos;s mission in Biomedical Research.</department_description><detailed_description>The Assistant Director, Treasury Services, will report to the Assistant Vice President of Finance and oversee the Treasury office, including the Treasury Manager and the Treasury Assistant/Cashier. Responsibilities include completing daily cash reviews, performing custody, private equity, and hedge fund Investments, preparing cash flow for nonmarketable securities, requesting Department of Justice and United States Department of Agriculture fund drawdowns through their respective websites, and posting receipts for the same in Oracle AR, accounts receivable reconciliation, providing the Development and Controllers Office with gift copies information for funds received through checking, tracking and sending notification of anticipated fund and stock transfers when received, and bank reconciliations for investment accounts. Year-end responsibilities include preparing entries to close investment purchases and sales into investment cost balances, managing expense, revenue, and adjustment trades accruals, and working on the Investment Roll forward schedule and Bond payment schedule and line of credit interest calculations and posting.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in accounting, finance, or related and a minimum of five years of experience in a treasury role required. Must have experience in accounting and recording treasury activity to the general ledger, excellent Excel skills and strong analytical skills, and strong interpersonal and communication skills to develop/maintain relationships with internal staff and, most notably, our outside banking contacts. A high degree of accuracy, attention to detail and confidentiality, ability to work independently or as a team member, and the ability to meet deadlines and able to pivot for items that become immediate is essential.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC26745</id><title>Receiving Clerk</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=26745&amp;p_spid=1063088</url><publish_date>02-Aug-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Purchasing</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Purchasing</professional_area><department_description>The Purchasing Department is responsible for the cost-effective and expeditious procurement of goods and services to support the scientific and administrative endeavors of the Rockefeller University.  The Rockefeller University Purchasing Department, along with the Receiving and Stockroom Departments, help ensure that equipment, supply and service needs of the University are  accomplished  in a professional manner that also adheres to all legal requirements and best business practices.
</department_description><detailed_description>The Receiving Clerk will be responsible for the receipt, scanning, and identification of all inbound Purchase Order (PO)-related packages and will be responsible for checking contents of the boxes against the University PO and vendor packing slips.  The Receiving Clerk will also be responsible for proper oversight of all PO-related outbound shipments. Will maintain the oversight of the UPS shipping manifest for all outbound Purchase Order-related packages, assist in the distribution of packages to the end-user, and obtain and maintain all related receiving documentation, including the associated filing system. The Receiving Clerk will also be responsible for maintaining the compressed cylinder inventory, backfill for the Stockroom and Mailroom, and assisting with special projects as needed.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required; Bachelor&apos;s degree preferred. Must have excellent customer service skills, written and verbal communication skills, and working knowledge of computers such as MS Office. Must be flexible and willing to take on additional assignments as required by the Receiving and Purchasing Department as necessary. FDNY C-14 certification is a plus.</job_requirements><additional_details>Must be able to lift, hold, or carry up to 40 pounds. Must be able to engage in a full range of motion, stand for extended periods, bend, push, pull, and reach above the shoulders.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment.  Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.&lt;/div&gt;</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27417</id><title>Laboratory Administrator (Part-time, 17.5 hours/week)</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27417&amp;p_spid=1095120</url><publish_date>08-Dec-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Genetically Encoded Small Molecules</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Administrative and Support Services</professional_area><department_description>Researchers in the Laboratory of Genetically Encoded Small Molecules are working on projects related to the human microbiome, bacterial small molecules and host microbial interactions. The lab&apos;s research is focused on identifying bacterial genes, pathways and molecules that influence host-cellular functions and developing these host-microbial interactions into novel treatments for human disease. To this end we focus on three major areas of research: 1) high throughput screening of bacterial metabolites and genes to identify effector functions, 2) mouse models of inflammatory and metabolic diseases and 3) in vivo validation of bacterial metabolites and genes in human cohorts.</department_description><detailed_description>The Laboratory Administrator will be responsible for fostering the efficient use and flow of financial and scientific resources in a high-level research environment and supporting the laboratory head in his day-to-day and long-term administrative responsibilities and scientific agenda. Responsibilities include overseeing the office and laboratory of the Principal Investigator (PI) working in a lab of 20-25 people, managing lab finances including budget accounting of several large accounts and private and federal grants, writing progress reports, and other administrative demands of grant applications, and preparing and structuring documents for acquisition of new private and federal funding opportunities. Will manage the PI&apos;s travel arrangements, manage and process orders and inventories, process all laboratory personnel appointments, including new hires and terminations, handle correspondence and interactions with government officials, collaborators, and Rockefeller University staff on laboratory matters, act as a laboratory liaison to the rest of the University, and maintain the lab website concerning lab news, publications, arrivals, departures, and CVs.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree and a minimum of three years of increasingly responsible administrative roles are required. Knowledge of grant writing and management and comfortability with budgets and basic accounting necessary. Excellent organizational skills, outstanding interpersonal and communication skills, and the ability to create and maintain strong working relationships in a team environment required. An innate ability to manage priorities and provide support in many areas and proficiency in Microsoft Office are necessary. Must be excited to work as an integral member of a highly productive and close-knit team and willing to take on a broad range of tasks.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27357</id><title>Research Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27357&amp;p_spid=1092120</url><publish_date>23-Nov-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Genetically Encoded Small Molecules</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>Researchers in the Laboratory of Genetically Encoded Small Molecules are working on projects related to the human microbiome, bacterial small molecules and host microbial interactions. The lab&apos;s research is focused on identifying bacterial genes, pathways and molecules that influence host-cellular functions and developing these host-microbial interactions into novel treatments for human disease. To this end we focus on three major areas of research: 1) high throughput screening of bacterial metabolites and genes to identify effector functions, 2) mouse models of inflammatory and metabolic diseases and 3) in vivo validation of bacterial metabolites and genes in human cohorts.</department_description><detailed_description>The Research Assistant will join members of the laboratory using methods from molecular biology, organic chemistry, and microbiology to access bioactive natural products and their respective biosynthetic gene clusters from the soil and human microbiomes. Will be responsible for using a range of techniques, including molecular biology, tissue culture, animal work (mouse), and chemistry. #INDRES21</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required; Master&apos;s degree and educational emphasis in biology, microbiology, biochemistry, or a related field preferred.  Must have previous experience working in a lab and experience with molecular biology and chemistry techniques, tissue culture, and animal work. Must be able to work collaboratively in a team environment as well as independently as necessary.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27333</id><title>Housing Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27333&amp;p_spid=1091116</url><publish_date>18-Nov-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Housing Office</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Administrative and Support Services</professional_area><department_description>Rockefeller University provides a variety of housing accommodations in support of the scientific needs of the University.  Apartments and dormitories are available to full-time faculty and students, and hotel accommodations are available for faculty and guests of the Rockefeller community.  The Housing Department provides a safe, secure, affordable residence that is conveniently located near the campus.  Most of the University&apos;s apartments are located in full-service apartment buildings, with door staff and a variety of amenities.  A few smaller apartment buildings are located within a short walking distance from campus.  Dormitories and guest accommodations are located on the main campus.  The Rockefeller campus is located on the Upper East Side, one of New York&apos;s most desirable residential neighborhoods.  The 45-person housing staff consists of a group of mechanics, porters, housekeepers, and doorpersons, a superintendent for each building, and an office staff to address administrative needs.</department_description><detailed_description>The Housing Office Assistant will be responsible for performing clerical and administrative duties. Responsibilities include establishing, maintaining, processing, and updating files, records, and other documents, sorting, and delivering departmental mail, and maintaining and filing tenant records. Will provide backup support to the Housing Receptionist, Purchasing Coordinator, and Guest Room Coordinator as needed.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required; Bachelor&apos;s degree preferred. Must have excellent interpersonal, organizational, and writing skills and the ability to work independently and cooperatively with others. Must be proficient in using computer programs for word processing, spreadsheets, database maintenance, and bookkeeping.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>504 East 63rd Street</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27418</id><title>Scientific Editor, JEM</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27418&amp;p_spid=1095121</url><publish_date>14-Dec-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Journal of Experimental Medicine (JEM)</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Publishing</professional_area><department_description>The Rockefeller University Press publishes three biomedical research journals: The Journal of Cell Biology, The Journal of Experimental Medicine, and The Journal of General Physiology. We are committed to identifying and publishing the highest quality research. All editorial decisions are made in conjunction with active academic scientists, and peer-review operations and pre-press production functions are carried out at the RUP offices.</department_description><detailed_description>The Journal of Experimental Medicine (JEM) seeks a talented individual to join the editorial team as a Scientific Editor or Senior Scientific Editor, dependent on work experience. JEM is a multidisciplinary journal, published by not-for-profit, academic publisher Rockefeller University Press (RUP), and dedicated to publishing high-quality research in experimental medicine and disease pathogenesis. Reporting to the Executive Editor, the Scientific Editor will oversee the peer-review process for submitted research papers, assess submitted research papers for scope, originality, rigor, context, and implications, and provide editorial recommendations. Will collaborate with other editors on the JEM team and experts on JEM&apos;s academic editorial board on all aspects of the editorial process, including manuscript selection and peer-review, represent JEM at national and international scientific conferences and research institutions, recruit high-quality content publishing in JEM, and establish relationships with researchers through outreach to the respective scientific communities and by providing excellent author service. Will commission reviews and other front-matter content for JEM and work closely with colleagues across RUP on press-wide initiatives.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Ph. D. degree in neuroscience or related field and a minimum of two years of editorial experience required. Must have a passion for science and an eagerness to learn about new research areas, a strong interest in scientific publishing and publication ethics, excellent critical thinking skills, and superb attention to detail.  A deep understanding of the field and eagerness to stay current with new trends and developments are necessary.  Excellent interpersonal, communication, networking, and organizational skills, required. Must be able to work successfully independently and in a diverse global team.  This position will require traveling to conferences and visiting research institutions when travel resumes.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required, including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>2nd Floor</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC26976</id><title>Bioinformatics Analyst</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=26976&amp;p_spid=1074099</url><publish_date>23-Sep-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Bioinformatics Resource Center</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>The Bioinformatics Resource Center (BRC) provides bioinformatics analysis, experimental design consultation, software infrastructure, and training to the scientific community at Rockefeller University. With specific expertise in the processing and analysis of high-throughput genomic sequencing data, and in collaboration with both wet and dry lab biologists, the BRC aims to support and accelerate the diverse and cutting-edge research conducted at the university through the creation of analytical pipelines; the analysis of biological data via direct collaborations; and the training of Rockefeller&apos;s faculty, students, and scientific staff.</department_description><detailed_description>The Bioinformatics Analyst will work within the Bioinformatics Resource Center to provide analysis support to research groups and to establish the bioinformatics infrastructure and training necessary to promote high-quality computational biology research within the university. The Bioinformatics Analyst will support the diverse range of biological data generated by research groups at The Rockefeller University by communicating bioinformatics analysis to students, postdoctoral trainees, research scientists, and principal investigators; always ensuring the validity and reliability of data and methods; and maintaining accurate and complete records of analysis projects. Will identify and develop suitable techniques for the analysis and visualization of data, build and maintain the associated computational resources (software packages, databases, or web-based analysis and visualization tools), and maintain all codes and programs used for analysis and tool development with suitable source control. The Bioinformatics Analyst will assist in the administration of the Bioinformatics facility&apos;s computational infrastructure, identify and implement present and upcoming infrastructure requirements for the Bioinformatics team, and develop and assist in bioinformatics training for staff and students at The Rockefeller University.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Ph.D. in computational biology, bioinformatics, or biological sciences required; educational emphasis in epigenetics preferred. Advanced training at the postdoctoral level or equivalent research, industrial or commercial experience preferred. Must be knowledgeable in molecular biology and genomics and have previous experience with bioinformatics techniques and tools used in these fields. Experience developing R and Bioconductor packages in the analysis of biological data required. Proficiency in the acquisition and analysis of high throughput sequencing data required and demonstrated high level of skill in at least one general programming language (Python, Java, or C++) necessary. Proven ability in software development and the collaborative use of source control is a plus. Previous experience training biologists and bioinformaticians in the use of bioinformatics tools, analyzing epigenetics data from high sequencing experiments, and contributing to peer-reviewed publications is desirable. Experience working with small RNAs and analysis of RNA-binding proteins and proficiency in web programming (Django, JavaScript) preferred.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC26848</id><title>Director Of Infrastructure</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=26848&amp;p_spid=1068091</url><publish_date>27-Aug-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Information Technology</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Information Technology</professional_area><department_description>The goal of Information Technology (IT) is to provide information resources and services to accelerate and support scientific research at The Rockefeller University. Under the aegis of the Office of the CIO, which is responsible for Information Technology, high-performance computing, bioinformatics, decision support systems, data analytics, cyber security, and the university&apos;s Library, the Director of Infrastructure will be a member of the Information Technology department&apos;s senior leadership team and report directly to the Chief Information Officer (CIO).</department_description><detailed_description>The Director of Infrastructure role is responsible for establishing the strategic and technical direction for the university&apos;s cyber-infrastructure, whenever possible advancing the university&apos;s adoption of a cloud first deployment philosophy and a serverless environment that appropriately leverages automation, DevOps methodologies, Site Reliability Engineering (SRE) principles, and containerization/virtualization to build and maintain robust, resilient, and highly available systems and service offerings. In this role, the candidate will have the oversight of several groups within the Information Technology department, including: the Platform Services and Cloud Services (PSCS) group, which is responsible for Active Directory, Enterprise Messaging (O365), Enterprise storage (currently NetApp and Data Domain), collaboration services (DropBox and OneDrive); Networking and Telecommunications, and Cloud and Container Engineering (CCE).</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree or equivalent experience in computer science, information systems/technology or a related technical or scientific field required; graduate degree preferred. Proven track record of successfully managing diverse technical staff required. Strong expertise in commercial cloud infrastructures (i.e. AWS, GCP, and Azure) and containerization (e.g. Docker, Kubernetes, Swarm) technologies is required. Experience in an academic computing environment or scientific laboratory highly desired. Familiarity with virtualization technologies and related tools (e.g. Vagrant, VirtualBox, VMware, VDI) a plus. Experience managing Linux/UNIX and Windows Enterprise services infrastructure with a diverse technical endpoint environment (Windows Server OS, Microsoft Exchange, RedHat/CentOS/Ubuntu, load balancers and proxy servers) required. Familiarity with networking infrastructure and protocols (e.g. TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP) required. Knowledge of both traditional telecommunications infrastructures (e.g. PBX) and VoIP and Unified Communications and Collaboration (UCC) technologies is preferred. Must have experience with establishing and maintaining high-quality enterprise system and service monitoring environments. Experience with collaborative automated test tools (e.g. Cucumber) desired. Should be familiar with code repositories such as GitLab. Must have the ability to prioritize based on the objectives of multiple groups and build strong relationships across teams. Working knowledge of modern programming languages and concepts (in order to facilitate an infrastructure-as-code environment) is strongly desired. Proven ability and passion for continuous learning, ability to critically evaluate new technologies. Understanding of Agile/Kanban techniques highly desired. Must possess a strong sense of ownership and accountability, along with a positive, constructive approach with an emphasis on collaboration and good execution.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27515</id><title>Data Services Librarian</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27515&amp;p_spid=1099138</url><publish_date>13-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Library</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Education and Library</professional_area><department_description>The mission of Markus Library is to support and enhance the University&apos;s research programs and to promote the reputation and influence of the University.  Utilizing its own extensive collections in the life sciences that support the research interests of the University, and a wide array of information resources licensed beyond the University, the Library is able to provide the faculty, staff and students scientific information support needed to advance their research goals.  Using technology, a variety of collaborative relationships, and networking and outreach activities, the library supports and advances scholarly communication and the advancement of knowledge.</department_description><detailed_description>The Data Services Librarian is primarily responsible for the development, implementation, outreach, and support of data Management activities at the Rockefeller University Library. This role encompasses developing and implementing a robust data management service that provides training, support, and assistance throughout the research data life cycle, including creating fundamental infrastructures such as data repository, data catalog, metadata schema, and ontology. The Data Services Librarian will work with the University Librarian, Assistant University Librarian, and Rockefeller IT Department to ensure that the appropriate services are developed, implemented, and improved upon and remain functional and relevant. Will be involved in the development and implementation of the Library&apos;s Embedded Librarian program and the search for an appropriate electronic notebook product for the University. The secondary role of the Data Services Librarian includes generating reports detailing research productivity (publications, preprints, etc.) as required for the Rockefeller University Administration and maintaining the author publication database. Will act as the Public Access Compliance Monitor for NIHMS/PMC and ensure all publications from Rockefeller University are compliant with all federal mandates regarding open access, provide support and guidance for scientists and lab managers, and develop training and workshops around this topic. As a part of the Library team, the Data Services Librarian will provide general reference services related to the various platforms offered by the Library, including but not limited to Scopus, Web of Science, PubMed, Scifinder, Pharmaprojects, Datacite, Endnote, Zotero, Libguides. This encompasses developing and maintaining Libguides relating to the various platforms, developing training sessions, providing group or one on one assistance, identifying new and relevant media to serve the Rockefeller University community better, producing emails/blog posts to update the Rockefeller University community on Library products and services, and assisting in the generation of reading lists for various on-campus seminar/lecture series. The Data Service Librarian will also staff the circulation desk and assist patrons on-site, via email, and virtually.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Master&apos;s Degree and educational emphasis in library/information science or another relevant advanced degree with experience in data management, scholarly communication, or the research lifecycle required; Ph.D. degree is preferred. Must have experience using current data management standards and best practices, data repository systems. Robust Microsoft Office suite, WordPress, Endnote/Zotero skills, required. Experience with scripting and programming languages (PHP, Perl, Python, R, etc.), preferred. Knowledge of metadata standards and other formats used in research (e.g., Dublin Core, DDI, ORCID, DOI) and knowledge of copyright and licensing issues related to data deposit and sharing is required. Must be familiar with data repository systems, experience in biological data repositories (e.g., GRO, SRA), preferred. Excellent verbal, written, and presentation communication skills, required. Must be detail-oriented, work quickly and independently, and have practical project management skills and time management skills. Experience working with biomedical and health sciences researchers, emphasizing informatics, scientific research, or managing research data, is preferred. Must be able to provide training on various platforms offered by the Library. Considerable knowledge of data management principles, including FAIR data and data sharing, tools available for researchers such as DMP Tool, and changes in the data management landscape from the perspective of funders and publishers are required to fulfill essential responsibilities.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27491</id><title>Research Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27491&amp;p_spid=1098134</url><publish_date>07-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Human Genetics of Infectious Disease</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>The Laboratory of Human Genetics of Infectious Diseases studies the genetics of human predisposition to pediatric infectious diseases, particularly mycobacterial diseases, invasive pneumococcal diseases and herpes simplex encephalitis. It aims to identify Mendelian &apos;holes&apos; in the immune defense of otherwise healthy children who are susceptible to specific infectious diseases, work that has profound implications for and has resulted in a paradigm shift in human clinical medicine and fundamental immunology. In the past decade, the laboratory has uncovered that single genetic lesions in children confer severe and selective vulnerability to certain illnesses, whereas corresponding infections in adults result more from polygenetic inheritance. This work not only blurs the distinction between patient-based Mendelian genetics and population-based complex genetics but has also provided experimental support for a unified theory of human infectious diseases.</department_description><detailed_description>The Research Assistant will work primarily under the direct supervision of a Senior Researcher of the lab investigating the human genetic basis of viral diseases and interact with other researchers of the group. Will be responsible for carrying out, reporting, and recording experiments that aim to identify and characterize genetic disorders of the immune system. Responsibilities will include analysis of databases, cloning and sequencing DNA, setting up and analyzing PCR experiments, tissue culture, and biochemical functional studies of the signaling pathways involved in antiviral immunity using various cell types.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required; Master&apos;s degree and educational emphasis in biochemistry, molecular genetics, immunology, or related field preferred. Must have a minimum of three years of experience and be detail-oriented, have a strong sense of responsibility, and work as part of a team in a fast-paced environment. Strong interpersonal skills, communication skills, and computer proficiency are required. Experience with Western blot and flow cytometry methods preferred.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Ave</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><postal_code>10065</postal_code><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27053</id><title>Laboratory Helper</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27053&amp;p_spid=1078096</url><publish_date>04-Oct-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Neural Systems</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>Our visual perception of the outer world is the creation of active brain processes that structure and select the information provided by the eyes. The Laboratory of Neural Systems is interested in the neural processes that form object representations as well as those that allow attention to make those representations available for cognition.  Our laboratory aims to understand the inner workings of this system, from the level of individual cells to the interactions of brain areas, in order to answer questions such as: How does face selectivity emerge in a single cell? How is information transformed from one face patch to another? What is the contribution of each face patch to different face recognition abilities like the recognition of a friend or a smile? How do the different face patches interact in different tasks? And how is information extracted from a patch when a perceptual decision is made?</department_description><detailed_description>The Laboratory Helper will prepare and sterilize experimental supplies and reagents, maintain inventory of general lab supplies, including record-keeping, submitting order requests, and re-stocking, organize and document chemical and biological substances, keep track of expiration dates, and coordinate with the Lab Safety Officer for hazardous waste disposal. Will maintain the functionality of general lab instruments (e.g., eyewash stations, suction system, NHP transport carts &amp;amp; chairs) and keep a clean and orderly working environment. Will assist with equipment inventory and maintenance and other routine or ad hoc organizational tasks.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required. General interest in working in a brain research laboratory is a must. Must have an excellent work ethic, be meticulous, reliable, and work independently after training. Good interpersonal, communication, and organization skills are required. Basic computer skills are a must. Must feel comfortable lifting or pushing heavy instruments weighing up to 50lbs.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC25001</id><title>Research Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=25001&amp;p_spid=984022</url><publish_date>13-Aug-2020</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>The Rockefeller University</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>&lt;div&gt;At Rockefeller University, bioscience is what we do. It&apos;s all we do. Our exclusive focus is on uncovering the processes that underlie life. How cells work. How genes are controlled. What makes us sick, and what keeps us healthy. The research underway in our labs today is leading to the breakthroughs that will transform medicine tomorrow. A place of both quiet contemplation and intense scientific energy, our unique campus is the backdrop to a culture that values both independence and collaboration. Discoveries made this year by Rockefeller scientists will someday lead to new medicines and help us conquer infectious diseases, cancer, neurodegenerative disorders, and many other afflictions. Each represents a step toward a future in which people live longer, healthier lives&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</department_description><detailed_description>The Research Assistant will work closely with senior scientists and participate in challenging, complex, and dynamic research projects. Will learn advanced lab techniques and build strong analytical skills. Responsibilities include performing experiments, presenting your work at laboratory meetings, journal clubs, conferences, and attending a rich program of scientific meetings, lectures, and special events. As a Research Assistant, you will be a more confident, directed, and competitive applicant for graduate/medical school. You will enjoy excellent compensation and benefits, including tuition reimbursement and free MCAT/GRE prep courses. Unspoken luxuries also include our intimate community, extreme prestige (number of Nobel prizes and laureates on-campus), incredible funding and core facilities, and the perks - state-of-the-art gym facility, health and wellness initiatives, inclusion in many affinity groups including diversity initiatives, science outreach, and research assistant community, river views and living in NYC! After two years, Research Assistants go on to the top Ph.D., M.D., and M.D./Ph.D. programs, while some choose to continue as a third-year researcher to learn more. </detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science and a passion for research required. Will consider a Master&apos;s degree. Previous laboratory experience preferred.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment.  Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27227</id><title>Research Specialist</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27227&amp;p_spid=1086110</url><publish_date>04-Nov-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Ruta Laboratory</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description> 
The Laboratory of Neurophysiology and Behavior takes advantage of the relatively simple nervous system of the fruit fly Drosophila to examine how flexibility is engineered into the nervous system to give rise to adaptive behaviors, at the level of both individuals and species. We examine how learning rapidly shapes neural pathways to allow each member of a species to respond appropriately to their unique experience of the world. We also consider how neural circuits are adapted over longer evolutionary time scales to give rise to species-specific behaviors. Our lab employs a multidisciplinary approach, from biochemistry to behavior, with the goal of revealing the neural basis for flexible behavior at high resolution.  
 
</department_description><detailed_description>The Laboratory of Neurophysiology and Behavior is seeking an experienced and talented molecular biologist who will contribute to ongoing work studying how neural circuits evolve across Drosophila species to mediate species-specific behaviors. The work will include designing and implementing different genome editing strategies, such as PiggyBac, PhiC31, and CRISPR-Cas9, to generate novel genetic reagents in non-model Drosophila species. Responsibilities include designing and constructing targeting vectors, screening transformants by fluorescent markers and/or genotyping, and Drosophila husbandry. Additional duties may consist of anatomic, functional, or behavioral characterization of generated lines. Will be an active contributor to research projects, including in the conceptual design and analysis of experiments, and presentation of data in laboratory meetings.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required; Master&apos;s degree and educational emphasis in molecular biology, genetics, or a closely related field preferred. Extensive experience in molecular biology, including CRISPR-Cas9 genome editing and experience designing complex cloning strategies and troubleshooting molecular biology experiments required. Must have excellent organizational, communication, and time management skills. Must be detail-oriented, highly organized, focused, a fast learner, and able to work within a team as well independently. Experience working with Drosophila and a solid foundation in fly genetics, desirable.  Expertise in a subset of the following techniques is highly desirable: DNA/RNA extraction, PCR (conventional, multiplex, touchdown, reverse transcription, genotyping), cloning (restriction enzyme, Gibson assembly, Gateway), CRISPR-Cas9 genome editing, Drosophila genetics, or Drosophila husbandry. Must be detail-oriented, focused, and able to work within a team as well as independently. The ability to be creative and stay abreast of advanced techniques in molecular biology and be proactive and take ownership of your work necessary.  Must be excited to contribute to innovative science, work independently and manage multiple projects concurrently.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27288</id><title>Part-time Laboratory Technician (18 hrs./week)</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27288&amp;p_spid=1089111</url><publish_date>09-Nov-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Ruta Laboratory</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description> 
The Laboratory of Neurophysiology and Behavior takes advantage of the relatively simple nervous system of the fruit fly Drosophila to examine how flexibility is engineered into the nervous system to give rise to adaptive behaviors, at the level of both individuals and species. We examine how learning rapidly shapes neural pathways to allow each member of a species to respond appropriately to their unique experience of the world. We also consider how neural circuits are adapted over longer evolutionary time scales to give rise to species-specific behaviors. Our lab employs a multidisciplinary approach, from biochemistry to behavior, with the goal of revealing the neural basis for flexible behavior at high resolution.  
 
</department_description><detailed_description>The Fly Food Facility supports several laboratories which are using the fruit fly (Drosophila) as a key model system to explore questions ranging from the evolution of novel genes to the intricacies of neural circuit computations. The Laboratory Technician will oversee and aid in the weekly production of fruit fly culture media, following established recipes and protocols and participate in some operational tasks of the facility. Responsibilities include operating equipment used for media preparation and food dispensing, delivering weekly fresh fruit fly media orders to fruit fly laboratories at the Rockefeller University, implementing and optimizing new media recipes based on evolving laboratory needs, coordinating weekly orders, and maintaining records of past orders.  Will manage the budget and send quarterly updates on spending to affiliated labs.</detailed_description><job_requirements>High School diploma or equivalent required; Bachelor&apos;s degree preferred.  Must have experience in the production of fly food or similar media, preferred.  Previous experience managing a budget necessary.  Must be highly reliable, careful, helpful, and meticulous about the work, with the ability to follow protocols accurately.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27228</id><title>Research Specialist</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27228&amp;p_spid=1086111</url><publish_date>04-Nov-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Ruta Laboratory</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description> 
The Laboratory of Neurophysiology and Behavior takes advantage of the relatively simple nervous system of the fruit fly Drosophila to examine how flexibility is engineered into the nervous system to give rise to adaptive behaviors, at the level of both individuals and species. We examine how learning rapidly shapes neural pathways to allow each member of a species to respond appropriately to their unique experience of the world. We also consider how neural circuits are adapted over longer evolutionary time scales to give rise to species-specific behaviors. Our lab employs a multidisciplinary approach, from biochemistry to behavior, with the goal of revealing the neural basis for flexible behavior at high resolution.  
 
</department_description><detailed_description>The Laboratory of Neurophysiology and Behavior is seeking an experienced biochemist that will work as part of a small team to carry out structure-function studies of olfactory receptors. The work will include designing and engineering expression vectors, receptor purification, and functional and structural characterization of their odorant tuning. To learn more about our group&apos;s work, please see our recent publication in which we provide insight into the structural basis of promiscuous odorant recognition.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required; Master&apos;s degree and educational emphasis in biochemistry, structural biology, pharmacology, or a closely related field preferred.  Must have several years of biochemistry experience purifying recombinant proteins from heterologous expression systems and optimizing purification conditions.  Experience with membrane protein purification is highly desirable. Must have a comprehensive understanding of protein chemistry and biochemistry methodologies, the ability to perform complex experiments with high reliability and accuracy with minimal supervision, and excellent organizational, communication, and time management skills. Must be detail-oriented, self-driven, and possess the experience and knowhow to troubleshoot experimental challenges. Experience with PCR, cloning, mammalian and insect tissue culture, baculovirus production, cell transfection and infection, affinity purification, fluorescence-detection size-exclusion chromatography, protein electrophoresis (Native, SDS-PAGE, and western blot), cell-based functional assays, and cryo-electron microscopy required. Experience with molecular modeling and protein structure predictions would be an asset but is not required. Must be a creative thinker, excited to work in a dynamic interdisciplinary environment, and be an active technical and conceptual contributor to a research program.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27189</id><title>Research Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27189&amp;p_spid=1084112</url><publish_date>01-Nov-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Kronauer Laboratory</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description></department_description><detailed_description>The Research Assistant will work closely with graduate students and post-doctoral fellows on various research projects focused on the neurobiology underlying chemical communication and social behavior in ants and the molecular mechanisms controlling individual differences in development and behavior. The Research Assistant will conduct molecular biology, neuroscience, and ethology techniques, including DNA and RNA sequencing, confocal and two-photon microscopy, as well as automated behavioral tracking and data analyses. The precise roles can be tailored to the interests of the Research Assistant. #INDRES21</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required.  Previous hands-on research lab experience, ideally in neuroscience, molecular biology, and/or histology preferred. Must be highly motivated, driven by scientific curiosity, and possess excellent organizational and interpersonal skills.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27096</id><title>Research Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27096&amp;p_spid=1080099</url><publish_date>12-Oct-2021</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Neurotechnology and Biophysics</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>The emergence of new optical technologies combined with molecular sensors and advanced computational tools has led to significant advances in understanding how the circuitry and dynamics of neuronal populations give rise to brain functions and behavior. The Laboratory of Neurotechnology and Biophysics (LNB) has a significant focus on developing and applying advanced optical imaging technologies with applications for systems neuroscience. Over the last few years, the lab has developed a portfolio of optical techniques that allow near-simultaneous stimulation and functional imaging of neuronal activity on the whole-brain level at the single-cell level in small model organisms and more recently in the more scattering rodent brain.
 </department_description><detailed_description>Working as part of a small team on the development of advanced neuroimaging technologies, the Research Assistant will contribute to the application of molecular tools in animal models. Will support the application of the lab&apos;s imaging technologies to rodents by conducting cranial window surgery, viral delivery of constructs, molecular biology and animal behavior, mouse colony management, and performing optical microscopy.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required; educational emphasis in neuroscience or molecular biology preferred. Must be highly motivated and have basic knowledge of rodent neuroanatomy and previous lab experience with rodents including cranial window surgery, and work with viral delivery of constructs. Basic knowledge and hands-on experience with molecular biology work including cloning, plasmid design, and sequencing highly desirable. Must be detail-oriented, highly organized, and able to manage multiple tasks and projects. Previous experience with rodent behavior or managing a colony preferred. Experience with one or more types of optical microscopy is preferred. Must have excellent verbal and written communication skills, self-motivation, enthusiasm for research, and thrive in a fast-paced environment. Must be able to work both independently and as part of a team.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>Floor B</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27518</id><title>Laboratory Manager</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27518&amp;p_spid=1099141</url><publish_date>13-Jan-2022</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Neurotechnology and Biophysics</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>The emergence of new optical technologies combined with molecular sensors and advanced computational tools has led to significant advances in understanding how the circuitry and dynamics of neuronal populations give rise to brain functions and behavior. The Laboratory of Neurotechnology and Biophysics (LNB) has a significant focus on developing and applying advanced optical imaging technologies with applications for systems neuroscience. Over the last few years, the lab has developed a portfolio of optical techniques that allow near-simultaneous stimulation and functional imaging of neuronal activity on the whole-brain level at the single-cell level in small model organisms and more recently in the more scattering rodent brain.
 </department_description><detailed_description>The Laboratory Manager will foster the efficient use and flow of financial and scientific resources in a high-level research environment. Will be supporting the head of the Laboratory in his day-to-day responsibilities and the administrative aspects of his long-term scientific agenda and vision. Responsibilities include overseeing the Office of the Principal Investigator (PI) and a laboratory of 10-15 scientists, autonomous management of the Laboratory&apos;s daily operations, and acting as the main point of contact for University staff on all administrative matters. Will assist the PI in formulating and implementing short and long-term goals for the operations of the Laboratory, project management, including assigning responsibilities, establishing timelines, monitoring progress of collaborative activities to ensure project milestones are met, and management of the Laboratory&apos;s recruitment. Will be responsible for managing laboratory finances, preparing monthly financial reports and projections, ordering supplies and equipment, and managing inventories. Will oversee several private and federal awards, including preparing, structuring, proofreading, editing, and submitting administrative documents for the acquisition of new grants, as well as their yearly progress and financial reports. Will manage the PI&apos;s schedule, correspondence and help with travel coordination.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree and a minimum of three years of increasingly responsible administrative roles required. Must be highly detail-oriented, dependable, results-oriented, forward thinking, have a strong sense of ownership for areas of responsibility, and have a high work ethic. Excellent organizational and communication skills, outstanding interpersonal skills, and the ability to create and maintain excellent working relationships within the lab and the broader University. Must be multi-faceted with an innate ability to manage priorities over long periods of time and provide support in multiple areas. Comfortability with budgets and basics of accounting knowledge is needed and prior experience with writing, editing and management of grants or other types of technical documents is highly desired. Full technical proficiency with Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>Floor B</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27490</id><title>Optical Engineer</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27490&amp;p_spid=1098133</url><publish_date>07-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Neurotechnology and Biophysics</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>The emergence of new optical technologies combined with molecular sensors and advanced computational tools has led to significant advances in understanding how the circuitry and dynamics of neuronal populations give rise to brain functions and behavior. The Laboratory of Neurotechnology and Biophysics (LNB) has a significant focus on developing and applying advanced optical imaging technologies with applications for systems neuroscience. Over the last few years, the lab has developed a portfolio of optical techniques that allow near-simultaneous stimulation and functional imaging of neuronal activity on the whole-brain level at the single-cell level in small model organisms and more recently in the more scattering rodent brain.
 </department_description><detailed_description>The Optical Engineer will consolidate a number of the optical neurotechnologies in our laboratory to support the development of alpha and beta prototype microscopes in collaboration with our industrial partners and to drive the broader dissemination of our technologies. Responsibilities include developing and optimizing new high-speed optical methods for large-scale recording of neuronal population activity, optimization and dissemination of computational imaging techniques, and imaging in and through scattering media.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required; Master&apos;s degree or Ph.D. preferred. Educational emphasis in physics, optical engineering, or related area and a minimum of two years of work experience in a scientific or industrial research environment is required. Must have basic programming skills, including Matlab, Python, LabView, and/or CAD. Experience in optical modeling and simulations, ultrafast laser systems, fiber optics, mechanical design, mechanical fabrication skills, RF electronics and electronics design, optomechanical hardware control (LabView, FPGA), large-scale data processing, and/or cluster computing is highly desirable. Must have excellent time management and communication skills, work in a team environment between academia and industry effectively, and a willingness to work outside of core expertise. Must be highly results-oriented, motivated, ambitious, and passionate about science.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>Floor B</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27512</id><title>Instrumentation Engineer</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27512&amp;p_spid=1099135</url><publish_date>13-Jan-2022</publish_date><employment_type>Full Time</employment_type><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Precision Instrumentation Technologies (PIT) Resource Center</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: rgb(13,13,13);font-family: Arial , sans-serif;font-size: 10.0pt;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;The Rockefeller University Precision Instrumentation Technologies (PIT) Resource Center enables high-end scientific instrument design and fabrication for the diverse research applications of the University&apos;s 70 Laboratories. Through interactive engagement with Rockefeller scientists, the PIT provides end-to-end service from conceptualization to application of scientific instrumentation. The PIT is staffed by a team with complementary expertise in optical design, mechanical design and fabrication, electronics design, and precision fabrication.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</department_description><detailed_description>The Instrumentation Engineer will join a team of experts in optical design, mechanical design and fabrication, electronics design, and precision fabrication and will interface with other PIT staff and/or engage directly with research laboratory scientists. Responsibilities will include supporting Rockefeller laboratories by realizing instrument solutions to address specific scientific needs, providing systems-level integration of different modules, including mechanical, electronic, and software components, and engaging with laboratories to identify and refine instrument designs. Will leverage available local and external fabrication resources to fabricate system modules; assemble, test, and document developed instrument solutions before they transition to the research laboratories; and interactively and iteratively troubleshoot designed instruments and implement required adjustments. Additional responsibilities will include participating in professional development opportunities to keep up-to-date with current technologies and preparing periodic written and verbal reports. The Instrumentation Engineer will be an integral member of a small and close-knit team and will take on a broad range of tasks, such as general administrative and maintenance duties related to facility operations, as needed.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in mechanical, optical, systems engineering, or a related field required. An enthusiasm for and a keen interest in scientific research and engineering, particularly the areas of neuroscience, biophysics, biology, physics, bioengineering, and/or electrical engineering, is a must. Must have a minimum of 3-5 years of increasingly responsible roles within a high-end engineering or scientific environment and at least two years of hands-on experience with mechanical workshop machinery, including CNC mill, lathe, and milling machines. Excellent working experience and knowledge of 3D mechanical design software such as SolidWorks, Autodesk Inventor, or related software a must. The ability to read, create, and revise technical drawings and work from drawings, including ones made by others, is required. Must have knowledge of and experience designing basic electronics circuits for hardware control, outsourcing electronics and mechanical designs efficiently, ideally with an established working relationship with several vendors, and programming languages such as MATLAB, Mathematica, or Python. Experience with microfabrication tools and techniques and rapid prototyping equipment (3D printer, laser cutter), preferred. Excellent organizational skills, outstanding interpersonal and communication skills, with the ability to create and maintain excellent working relationships in a team environment. Must be flexible, results-oriented, and willing to accomplish set goals.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>Plaza Building, Floor A</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27532</id><title>Research Support Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27532&amp;p_spid=1100135</url><publish_date>14-Jan-2022</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Precision Instrumentation Technologies</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: rgb(13,13,13);font-family: Arial , sans-serif;font-size: 10.0pt;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;The Rockefeller University Precision Instrumentation Technologies (PIT) Resource Center enables high-end scientific instrument design and fabrication for the diverse research applications of the University&apos;s 70 Laboratories. Through interactive engagement with Rockefeller scientists, the PIT provides end-to-end service from conceptualization to application of scientific instrumentation. The PIT is staffed by a team with complementary expertise in optical design, mechanical design and fabrication, electronics design, and precision fabrication.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</department_description><detailed_description>The Research Support Assistant will engage in high-end scientific instrument design and fabrication for the diverse research applications of the University&apos;s 70 laboratories. Will support laboratories by effective use of and training on PIT equipment and tools with a focus on makerspace equipment and tools, assist PIT staff in the fabrication, assembly, testing, and documentation of developed instrumentation solutions before they transition to the research laboratories, interactively and iteratively troubleshoot designed instruments and implement required adjustments, maintain and organize equipment, inventory, and stock materials, and provide general lab upkeep as necessary. Focus on safety concerning all people and lab equipment at all times.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree and educational emphasis in mechanical, optical, systems engineering, or a related field required. Must have familiarity with 2D and 3D mechanical design software such as SolidWorks, Autodesk Inventor, and hands-on experience with 3D printers (FFF, MJP, DLP). Knowledge of common scientific programming languages such as MATLAB, Python, or C/C++, experience with microcontrollers or single board computers including Arduino or Raspberry pi, hands-on experience with mechanical workshop machinery including lathe, milling machines, CNC mills, laser cutters, experience with microfabrication tools and techniques, and technical proficiency with Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Adobe Illustrator or Photoshop highly desired. Excellent organizational, time management, interpersonal and communication skills, and the ability to create and maintain excellent working relationships in a team environment necessary. Must be a results-oriented, innovative problem solver with enthusiasm for and a keen interest in scientific research and engineering, in particular in the areas of neuroscience, biophysics, biology, physics/optics, bioengineering, and/or electrical engineering. Must be excited to work as an integral member of a small, dynamic, close-knit team and willing to take on a broad range of tasks as needed.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>Plaza Building, Floor A</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27311</id><title>Executive Assistant</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27311&amp;p_spid=1090114</url><publish_date>11-Nov-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Brivanlou Laboratory</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Administrative and Support Services</professional_area><department_description>The ultimate objective of the work in my laboratory is to understand the cellular and molecular basis of vertebrate embryonic induction, with a special emphasis on germ layer and organ formation. Toward this aim we perform comparative studies using both amphibian and mammalian model systems, including human embryonic stem cells.</department_description><detailed_description>The Executive Assistant will provide direct support to the Head of the Laboratory and be responsible for all communication, correspondence, phone calls, and calendar coordination, personal assistance, appointment scheduling, and arranging international and domestic travel and meetings, including detailed itineraries, and event and conference organization. Additional duties include supply ordering, helping prepare technical presentations, and liaising with administrative departments such as Human Resources, IT, and the Office of Technology Transfer. Will assist the Laboratory Manager and other laboratory personnel as needed.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree required. Must have a minimum of two years of relevant administrative experience in a high-volume dynamic office environment.  Knowledge of operating systems and software in a Mac environment, demonstrated skill using a wide variety of software including Microsoft Suite, database processing, budget management, and calendar coordination required. Must be able to anticipate administrative issues and execute resolutions effectively and efficiently. Must possess excellent communication skills (written and verbal English skills), a professional phone demeanor, strong organizational and problem-solving skills, ability to work independently, and maintain confidentiality required. Event and travel planning experience is a plus. Previous experience in an academic setting desired.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job><job><id>IRC27451</id><title>Research Specialist</title><url>https://recruit.rockefeller.edu/OA_HTML/OA.jsp?page=/oracle/apps/irc/candidateSelfService/webui/VisVacDispPG&amp;p_svid=27451&amp;p_spid=1096134</url><publish_date>21-Dec-2021</publish_date><LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT>Synthetic Embryology</LAB_OR_DEPARTMENT><professional_area>Science</professional_area><department_description>The ultimate objective of the work in my laboratory is to understand the cellular and molecular basis of vertebrate embryonic induction, with a special emphasis on germ layer and organ formation. Toward this aim we perform comparative studies using both amphibian and mammalian model systems, including human embryonic stem cells.</department_description><detailed_description>The Research Specialist will work closely with postdoctoral researchers performing various molecular (e.g., cloning) and biochemical procedures, as well as microscopy in support of two current NIH marmoset monkey-related grant proposals. Will have wet bench responsibilities and some administrative support functions and assist with culturing stem cells and data analysis.</detailed_description><job_requirements>Bachelor&apos;s degree in science required; Master&apos;s degree and educational emphasis in biology, biophysics, or biochemistry preferred. Experience working in a research laboratory is required. Must possess outstanding organizational skills and an ability to prioritize tasks and activities. Must be highly focused and detail-oriented to carry out complex experiments.  Must demonstrate accuracy in record-keeping and organize, analyze, and calculate data.  Excellent verbal, written, and electronic communication skills and the ability to interact effectively in a collaborative work environment are necessary.</job_requirements><additional_details>This job requires that employees be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 as a condition of employment. Rockefeller University provides reasonable accommodations where legally required including accommodations for medical conditions and sincerely held religious beliefs.</additional_details><locations><location><street_address>1230 York Avenue</street_address><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><country_code>US</country_code></location></locations></job></jobs>